<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mrs. Jayme Davis on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</title>
    <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/people/mrs.-jayme-davis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mrs. Jayme Davis on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2013-{year} David E. Williams. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 00:05:43 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/people/mrs.-jayme-davis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 11, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-11-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 00:05:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-11-2020/</guid>
      <description>Took kids to bus stop. Went into work for an hour and then headed to SAIC for software meeting. Got back to Scientia and worked the day until late and then left to pick up the kids. Got home and ate supper. Took Ashley to Bedford North Lawrence for the varsity game, they honored elementary school basketball players and cheerleaders at halftime by allowing them onto the court. She met up with Mrs Davis and I tried to hang back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 7, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-7-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 23:58:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-7-2019/</guid>
      <description>Slept until 8am, surprised at that. Stopped by PO Box and picked up another letter from Daniel om my way to take the kids to get hair cuts at Fantastic Sams. The boys wanted their hair cut short so we did the #4 on top and #2 on side summer cut. Ashley wanted bangs, stylist checked and said it wouldn&amp;#8217;t work very well, so she got her ends trimmed as originally planned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 5, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-5-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 23:05:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-5-2019/</guid>
      <description>Work and school. Had a map meeting at 11:00am to discuss maps and map resources and didn&amp;#8217;t get out until 2:00pm! Lesa went to the dentist, got a clean and polish, no cavities. I got a text from Mrs Davis saying Ashley was in trouble and would have to sit out a game tonight, and that Mr Hudson would be calling me about it. Saw where I had a missed Springville call and called him back, he was in a meeting and would get back to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 2, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-2-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:02:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-2-2019/</guid>
      <description>Back to work and school. We suffered today. I picked up the mail from the PO Box, another letter from Daniel. Same old, same old. How he&amp;#8217;s sorry, how he loves the kids so much, how he wishes the kids would forgive him and write back. He pretends he cares about the kids, pretends to be sorry, but in reality his letters are all about him. We see typical addict behavior and mentality and we suspect the sudden burst of letters has to do with a program of some sort and he&amp;#8217;s hoping to gain an early release or something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 5, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-5-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 22:56:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-5-2019/</guid>
      <description>Election Day, no school, dropped kids off at daycare. Received email overnight that mail had arrived at the PO Box so I went and got it after dropping them off. Had five letters all from Daniel with each one directed to the kids. The dates were Oct. 2, 10, 18, 25 and Nov. 1. I worked in Bloomington and tied to get access to NGA maps, submitted request and awaiting the Need-to-Know confirmation from Navy sponsor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 4, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-4-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 23:03:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-4-2019/</guid>
      <description>Kids wanted to sleep an extra hour again &amp;#8211; me too! Got them to school on time and headed to work. Went to Best Buys and got a CAC reader and then headed to SAIC. Finished the day out there and then picked up Dillan and Bruce from daycare. Home game against Parkview, Ashley was cheerleading, Dwyane was in Hornets Nest. Mrs Davis texted Ashley forgot her bow so went home and looked but didn&amp;#8217;t see it so went to game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 29, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-29-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 23:01:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-29-2019/</guid>
      <description>Another day at Camp Atterbury, two down, two to go. Left Atterbury early and headed to Scientia and tested a new build and actually got home before dark! Text from Mrs Davis: Dillan filled his test paper with emojis and turned it in. Then he typed random gobbledygook on a second paper; F&amp;#8217;s of course. I told him since he doesn&amp;#8217;t want to do school work I was going to make him do real work and he seemed okay with that, so I had him dig a hole in the woods for an hour &amp;#8211; he didn&amp;#8217;t make the hour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 20, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-20-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 23:44:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-20-2019/</guid>
      <description>Friday, kids rode bus. Drove Suburban, miss is gone, fixed for $56, happy. Worked in Bloomington until 11:00, then drove disk to SAIC, tested and left for the day. Picked up Lesa, and we went to school for Grandparent&amp;#8217;s Day. As we walked in Mr Hudson intercepted us and pointed Dillan out sitting in the office, he hit Ashley in the back, and when he was told to stop, he got mad, threw a ball that hit a bucket that hit a girl in the mouth and busted her lip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 29, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-29-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 22:02:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-29-2019/</guid>
      <description>Barely made the bus, Kim waited for the kids to get on board. Took an alternate, scenic route to work, highway under construction and down to one lane. Spent most of day doing research. Lesa having her own problems at work. Both of us pretty zoned out by the time we get home. Mrs. Davis texted us, Dillan punched William in the eye and got in trouble for it. I was none to happy!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>