<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bruce on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</title>
    <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/people/bruce/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bruce on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2013-{year} David E. Williams. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 01:52:38 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/people/bruce/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 27, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-27-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 01:52:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-27-2020/</guid>
      <description>Worked until 3a last night / this morning, didn&amp;#8217;t get much sleep and when I did I dreamed about work, back at work by 9a and worked until 8:30p tonight &amp;#8211; finally got my patch out the door. I&amp;#8217;m exhausted! Put in 36.5 hours in the last three days! Considering I was on Spring Break Monday and Tuesday that&amp;#8217;s a good deal, only using 3.5 hours of PTO which leaves me over a week of vacation in the bank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 26, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-26-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 00:57:40 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-26-2020/</guid>
      <description>Worked from home, started at 8am, finished at midnight, took a lunch and dinner break, a 15 hour workday, but I got my patch out. Will need to go into the office tomorrow to test and install. Hoping to spend as little as possible in the office and going to bring a lot home with me. Ashley upset with the boys over a fort in the woods they destroyed supposedly to make it better which never happened.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 25, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-25-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 23:39:44 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-25-2020/</guid>
      <description>Went into work, Lesa got up with me, kids still sleeping when I left. Lesa home for the next 45 days or so. I wound up working until 5:30 and then I went to Walmart with Lesa&amp;#8217;s grocery list. Finally got home at 8:30pm with a truckload of supplies. Lesa is worried for my health and possible exposure to COVID-19. Lesa said the kids did okay but there was more friction between her and Ashley but not out-and-out fighting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 24, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-24-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 00:27:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-24-2020/</guid>
      <description>Last day of Spring Break for me. Lesa had a video conference with work, she&amp;#8217;s considered essential personnel, will round-robin Wednesdays with her co-workers and work from home the remainder of the time, and she&amp;#8217;ll get time-and-a-half when she does go into the office. I still have the desecration to work from home if I wish and am exempt from Governor&amp;#8217;s restrictions because I&amp;#8217;m a Department of Defense employee. It helps knowing our paychecks and jobs are secure for a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 23, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-23-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 01:42:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-23-2020/</guid>
      <description>Slow morning. Lesa gave me an Amazon FireTV Stick she got from somewhere? I got it working and it&amp;#8217;s just barely usable but it is usable. Watched a movie but I don&amp;#8217;t remember the name. Nice day so we all got out, Ashley read a book on the deck. Lesa, the boys, and myself got a lot of the recyclables together and I hauled a crap ton of plastic bottles. Took the kids with because the risk was low and there was no contact with people or things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 22, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-22-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 22:21:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-22-2020/</guid>
      <description>Church was live-streamed although we didn&amp;#8217;t watch. Instead we did our own church, sang songs, and Lesa had a lesson for us. It worked out pretty good. Made it to Lowe&amp;#8217;s and got the right faucet. I went to Aldi&amp;#8217;s looking for TP, milk, pizza rolls, chicken tenders, and mashed potatoes &amp;#8211; had nada. Went to Walmart and they had everything but the mashed potatoes. Got home and fixed the faucet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 21, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-21-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 22:16:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-21-2020/</guid>
      <description>Tried to sleep in, didn&amp;#8217;t happen. Ashley made me coffee and Lesa made me breakfast. Bruce was horsing in the kitchen or maybe helping, I&amp;#8217;m not sure which, but he ran into Lesa who had a pan and he surface burned his arm on the pan, sunburn is worse and he didn&amp;#8217;t phase him. I went to Lowe&amp;#8217;s to get an outdoor faucet because Dillan broke ours, don&amp;#8217;t ask me how, I don&amp;#8217;t know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 20, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-20-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 00:55:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-20-2020/</guid>
      <description>Repeat of yesterday. I went into Scientia, only one there half the day, one other co-worker came in. Lesa worked from home and watched the kids. All the kids except Dillan have their homework packets done. Mrs Malone called and talked to Ashley. Lesa took the kids to Springville Elementary playground, then to Springville Park, then to the park by Johnny&amp;#8217;s Junction &amp;#8211; each time they left when other people arrived.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 19, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-19-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:50:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-19-2020/</guid>
      <description>Ate breakfast with the family and then I went to work. Started at SAIC and then headed to Scientia, just two of us in the office, worked a 9-hour day. One of my co-workers was hospitalized with COVID-19 symptoms and difficulty breathing, scary sh*t. Picked up another letter from Daniel. Lesa worked from home and watched the kids. Sounds like it went mostly okay. Ashley said she didn&amp;#8217;t fight with Lesa at all, Lesa didn&amp;#8217;t say otherwise so proud of both of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 18, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-18-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 23:53:09 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-18-2020/</guid>
      <description>Day two of working from home. Lesa went in again today. Didn&amp;#8217;t get near the same done as I did yesterday. Since got stuff running though so by end of the day I&amp;#8217;ll have my time in. It rained all day long so the kids were stuck inside. Ashley&amp;#8217;s throat still raw but got better as the day went on, tea and honey helped. Dillan took a half hour rinse off shower and I had to yell at him to get out, Bruce &amp;#8220;accidentally&amp;#8221; shut Dwyane&amp;#8217;s hand in the door, and Bruce &amp;#8220;accidentally&amp;#8221; stepped on Ashley &amp;#8211; all before 10am!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 17, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-17-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 22:30:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-17-2020/</guid>
      <description>Lesa went into work, I worked from home and watched the kids. I got 7.5 hours of work done which is kind of amazing considering. In the morning the boys went outside and played in the mud until I chased them out of the yard and into the woods to dig. Ashley played in her room with &amp;#8230; well, I&amp;#8217;m not sure what. We had Vienna Sausages for lunch, their pick, I ate the barbecue ones, had pop-cycles afterward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 16, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-16-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 22:48:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-16-2020/</guid>
      <description>Bizarre day to say the least. Lesa went into work. I got kids ready and took them to daycare and then I went into work. Not many people at work, one co-worker came in, said he didn&amp;#8217;t feel well, and left. Two others left midday leaving me by myself. I worked a full day and then picked up the kids. Annetta said they were all good and the next time they&amp;#8217;re at daycare she&amp;#8217;ll get them some ice cream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 15, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-15-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 23:03:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-15-2020/</guid>
      <description>I woke up in a fever, took my temp, it was okay. Church canceled Sunday School, evening worship, Wednesday activities, everything but 10:30 worship service. They live-streamed the service. They also changed the way we do communion and offering. Pretty sparse attendance. We kept the kids with us. Right after church we went to Walmart and stocked up on more stuff. Couldn&amp;#8217;t find cereal or bread so hit three Dollar Generals on the way home from Walmart and still didn&amp;#8217;t find any.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 14, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-14-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 22:17:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-14-2020/</guid>
      <description>Stayed home all morning. I was listening to Flatt &amp;amp; Scruggs Live at Neely Auditorium on Vanderbilt University in Nashville, TN from May 2, 1963 and that kind of got the kids fired up. It turned into YouTube and hip-hop and others, and that of course turned into dancing and videos. The pinewood derby was supposed to be today but was canceled so we did something different. Played Words with Friends game (it&amp;#8217;s like Scrabble) with Ashley and only beat her by 6 points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 13, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-13-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 23:19:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-13-2020/</guid>
      <description>School and work. Had a hard time getting motivated at work. Was going to leave early but wound up staying later. School robocalled to say school is closed due to COVID-19 and won&amp;#8217;t be open until April. When I picked up kids I talked to Jessica about what we could expect daycare to do and it looks like unless sickness hits them it will be an option for us. Both our workplaces are being flexible so I think we&amp;#8217;ll be okay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 12, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-12-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:30:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-12-2020/</guid>
      <description>School and work. Lots of COVID-19 talk everywhere, it&amp;#8217;s on everyone&amp;#8217;s mind, most people trying not to panic, some people are simply idiots. Wondering whether we should cancel our Spring Break trip, Lesa looking to me to keep us all safe, kids are blissfully unaware of the danger. Getting pressure to step up my game at work; the office is more than half empty. Ditto for Lesa&amp;#8217;s work, many people wanting to or already are working from home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 11, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-11-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:28:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-11-2020/</guid>
      <description>Woke up exhausted, didn&amp;#8217;t want to get up, finally did. Stayed exhausted throughout the day, wound up working over even so. Jason texted and wanted to come to our house to cut pinewood derby cars, got home and he was already waiting in our drive, we cut the cars and the boys painted already, I polished the axles so they might go faster. Lesa went and got milk after dinner. Kids on devices or taking showers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 10, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-10-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 23:10:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-10-2020/</guid>
      <description>Took kids to school. Spent the entire day at SAIC. Lesa back at work, sent me email IU is closing classes after Spring Break and almost everyone will be working remotely. Pulled a nine hour day and then picked up kids from daycare, I&amp;#8217;m utterly exhausted. Slept much of the evening on the couch. Kids watched television and played and made much noise which irritated me. Jason Sowder was going to cut pinewood derby cars for me and the boys but cancelled earlier in the afternoon, hopefully tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 9, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-9-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 23:29:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-9-2020/</guid>
      <description>Took kids to school. Worked half a day at Scientia, other half at SAIC. Lesa took the day off, DST blues. She went shopping for supplies, hopefully enough to get us through two weeks of Coronavirus disease (COVID-19) epidemic but I doubt it. No troubles at school or daycare. Picked kids up and came home, Lesa had supper made. We ate and I took the boys to Cub Scouts. Dwyane packed care packages for the Bedford Police Department.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 8, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-8-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 23:43:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-8-2020/</guid>
      <description>Everyone more tired than usual due to DST and losing an hour. Went to church, didn&amp;#8217;t serve or teach. After lunch Lesa went to Rural King in Bedford looking for a larger drop pan which they didn&amp;#8217;t have, and she went to CVS as well. Ashley had a meltdown over her birthday and the amount of gifts she can have. The kids rode bikes a lot, it was a beautiful day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 7, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-7-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 23:19:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-7-2020/</guid>
      <description>Lazy-ish morning. Took the kids and went to Fayetteville to sign up boys for baseball, considering softball for Ashley. Kids played in giant sand pile while I did paperwork and got themselves filthy, then dumped their shoes and pants in the truck, Bruce on the seat. We all went to Dillan&amp;#8217;s basketball game, I had to leave with Ashley after the third quarter to take her to Amanda&amp;#8217;s &amp;#8211; they&amp;#8217;re going to Kroger on Liberty Drive for their last Girl Scout cookie booth, she sold 144 boxes her share for a total of 506 boxes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 6, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-6-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 23:38:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-6-2020/</guid>
      <description>Friday, dropped kids off, Lesa and I both worked, I was in Bloomington today. Lesa got off early, went grocery shopping, then picked up the boys from daycare. She came home, put up groceries, and took the boys to Burger King for supper. Then off to Mom and Son Nerf Wars at 1st Baptist in Bedford! They had Nerf gun fights, obstacle courses, bouncy houses, snacks and drinks. They had a blast, didn&amp;#8217;t even want to leave to go to Jiffy Treat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 5, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-5-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 23:21:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-5-2020/</guid>
      <description>Took kids to school, Dillan had his poster. Worked at SAIC all day. Bruce ate lunch in the office, Mr Hudson wasn&amp;#8217;t there, missed recess too. Stopped by PO Box on a whim and had two letters from Daniel, didn&amp;#8217;t get the usual notification I had mail. Picked up kids from daycare, nothing unusual there, Ashley upset she didn&amp;#8217;t get rewarded for cleaning up. Kind of cold outside so kids stayed in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 4, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-4-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 23:21:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-4-2020/</guid>
      <description>I took kids to the bus stop and came back home. Lesa and I both went to talk to Dwyane&amp;#8217;s Speech Therapist Darren Swango at Springville Elementary. Got to hear the kids announcements. Dwyane is doing really good, intermittent trouble with sh sounds. Afterward we talked about Dillan&amp;#8217;s speech, he can pronounce sounds okay but tends to go to fast, run words together, and kind of mumbles his words making him difficult to understand &amp;#8211; don&amp;#8217;t we know it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 3, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-3-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 23:56:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-3-2020/</guid>
      <description>Dropped kids at school. Went to work, Kind of a nerve-racking day. Really nice outside. Picked up kids, no major daycare issues to speak of, Bruce did get mouthy with Jessica so we talked about that. Dillan put hands on a kid at school and got called out for it by Mr Hudson. Kids played outside until dinner. Dillan said Ashley has a thing for his friend Bo from school so we teased her about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 2, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-2-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 22:43:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-2-2020/</guid>
      <description>Took kids to school, Ashley had a big box of cookies. Work, ugh! Nice day temp-wise but rained most of the day, thunder and lightning as I type this. Kathy Mitchell came to work and got her cookies from me. I picked up kids and headed home. Boys didn&amp;#8217;t want to go to Cub Scouts but we kind of made them, once there they had fun per usual. Ashley&amp;#8217;s tooth hurting from her spacer and she&amp;#8217;s been complaining about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 1, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-1-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 22:05:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-1-2020/</guid>
      <description>Skipped church, multiple people messaging wanting to know if we&amp;#8217;re okay &amp;#8211; we are. Slept until my Sunday alarm which hardly ever happens &amp;#8211; the kids or Lesa or the dogs almost always wake me up before. Ashley and me cooked breakfast for Lesa, Dwyane, and ourselves. Ashley, Dwyane, and myself played Yahtzee. Planned on doing something outdoors like hiking but it never happened. Kids rode bikes, Ashley and me mucked Oreo and Blackie&amp;#8217;s hutch, Lesa did some yard work so we were outdoors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 29, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--february-29-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 02:48:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--february-29-2020/</guid>
      <description>Everyone slept in a bit longer than usual &amp;#8211; usual is 6-7, today 7-8. Lazy morning, turned on radio, then got song requests, then the dancing. Lesa and Ashley went to get their hair cut, everyone booked up, even Walmart. Went to Taco Bell for lunch. Boys watched TV and I took a nice hot shower. Haircuts a bust so girls came home. Boys and myself had lunch. We all went to Walmart to get shoes and soup, weird combination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 28, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-28-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 01:00:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-28-2020/</guid>
      <description>Dropped kids at school, Bruce took his big helicopter for Show-and-Tell. Work. Took off late and went to the bank to deposit Girl Scout cookie checks, then Dollar General for Mt. Dews and antifreeze, losing 1&amp;frasl;2 a gallon a day, don&amp;#8217;t see a leak so it must be going out the tailpipe. Picked up kids from daycare. Lesa grocery shopped after work and we helped her carry in. Then everyone went into cleaning mode while Lesa got supper together &amp;#8211; we had pizza &amp;#8211; it is Friday night after all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 27, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-27-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 00:11:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-27-2020/</guid>
      <description>Took kids to school, side roads were really slick and icy, the main roads were not as bad. Got to work about 10 minutes late, worked until 4:30 and headed to pick up kids. Warmed up to where I didn&amp;#8217;t worry about the roads. My heater was blowing cold air, I lost a gallon of coolant in a day&amp;#8217;s time, going to have to check that out, hope it&amp;#8217;s not a head gasket but kind of suspect it could be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 26, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-26-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:12:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-26-2020/</guid>
      <description>Didn&amp;#8217;t snow that bad, roads were fine. Lesa off, and I took a half day. We dropped kids off at the bus stop and then we headed to Bloomington for Lesa&amp;#8217;s colonoscopy. She did fine, was a little confused after coming too, then a bit dizzy/weak until she ate something. It started snowing harder come noon and I wound up just taking the whole day off. Picked up the kids from school and we ate supper then I took all the kids to Minute to Win It at church.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 25, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-25-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:04:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-25-2020/</guid>
      <description>Rained in the morning but finally stopped. Now we&amp;#8217;re expecting a winter storm &amp;#8211; snow and ice overnight. Somehow managed to make the entire day at work, won&amp;#8217;t say I actually worked the entire day. Took kids to school of course. Wreck was still on the kid&amp;#8217;s mind. Lesa prepped for her colonoscopy, has to be there by 8am in the morning and she&amp;#8217;s really stressing over it. Got mad at Dillan over his grades.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 24, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-24-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 23:49:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-24-2020/</guid>
      <description>Rainy days and Mondays. Got kids to school okay. Went to SAIC, stayed all day. I&amp;#8217;m sick, have a cold, my nose is runny and my head stopped up, being sick sucks. Left SAIC early and picked up kids from school and headed home and took a nap while the kids watched TV. Lesa got home and we ate supper. The boys had a Pack meeting, Bruce did a skit with his den mates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 23, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-23-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 23:12:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-23-2020/</guid>
      <description>Up late last night, tired all day. Lesa kept letting the dogs in and out of the bedroom and I didn&amp;#8217;t even get to sleep until my alarm went off. Lesa stayed home from church, I was lockup deacon so we were the last ones out. Went home, got changed, and ate lunch. Dillan, Ashley, Bruce and myself went to the Tusseys. From there we went to Linda and Gordon Andersons&amp;#8217; house and picked up two huge turkeys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 22, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-22-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 02:29:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-22-2020/</guid>
      <description>Got up at 9, amazing! Ashley made me eggs-in-a-basket and Lesa made me coffee, I am loved. Took Ashley to Johnny&amp;#8217;s Junction and handed her off to Amanda. They did a cookie booth at Kroger on South Walnut in Bloomington, and then they went to Wendy&amp;#8217;s for lunch, and then to Amanda&amp;#8217;s to drop off cookies, and then they went to World Thinking Day in Williams, Indiana. Sounds like she had a lot of fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 21, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-21-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 23:59:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-21-2020/</guid>
      <description>The kids pissed me off so bad this morning. They are total butts! I sent them into school without a hug or kiss. First time I&amp;#8217;ve ever done that. Worked at SAIC all day, it sucked. I didn&amp;#8217;t want to pick the kids up come quitting time. First time I&amp;#8217;ve felt that way too. Asked Annetta what she would charge me to take them for the entire weekend. Stopped by TK, turned in paperwork and left a deposit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 20, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-20-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 23:39:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-20-2020/</guid>
      <description>Lesa left kind of early even for her, wondered what was up with that. Got the kids ready and waited for the bus with them. Headed into work. At 11:36am, got a call, and my day was ruined. Went to SAIC to put out fires, mostly did so, but will be going back again tomorrow. Worked later than I wanted but finally got out and picked up the kids. Eastern Greene had their open house tonight and we went.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 19, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-19-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 00:42:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-19-2020/</guid>
      <description>Kids too slow getting ready, boys playing Nerf guns and watching TV instead of getting ready. Ashley dragging her feet a little bit as well but she has a lot more stuff to do. Dropped the kids at school and headed into work. It got a bit stressful come afternoon but not too bad. Left late at 5pm and picked up kids. Nothing planned or scheduled for the evening. Lesa helped all the kids with their homework.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 18, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-18-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 23:27:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-18-2020/</guid>
      <description>Got the kids up and ready for school, just made the bus, it was a bit early and we were a bit late &amp;#8211; Ashley had to go back in for her glasses. Lesa and I took the day off so I went back home and crawled back into bed. Got up at 9am and by 10 we were headed to Greenfield to check out TK Construction&amp;#8217;s Jackson model home. Got there before they opened so we ate lunch at O&amp;#8217;Charlies, we both had Atlantic Salmon but prepared differently, it was very tasty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 17, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-17-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 23:31:40 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-17-2020/</guid>
      <description>President&amp;#8217;s Day, kids would normally have off but they have school to make up a snow day. Lesa worked and doesn&amp;#8217;t get the day off. I got the day off but worked anyway, and am trading it for tomorrow off. Lesa and I are going to tour the TK Jackson house in Greenfield &amp;#8211; they are closed Mondays. So, I worked all day at Scientia and was by myself all day, it was awesome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 16, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-16-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 23:04:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-16-2020/</guid>
      <description>We went to church, I was a teacher in Junior Church, Dwyane didn&amp;#8217;t want to participate during songs and copped an attitude when I tried to get him involved, Bruce interacted with me, Ashley befriended a little girl who was obviously very timid, Ashley took her hand and stayed with her the entire time, proud of her for showing empathy. Ashley had her Riley prayer slot at noon and took the time to pray for Riley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 15, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-15-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:22:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-15-2020/</guid>
      <description>Slept until 8 or so, kids started to make us breakfast in bed but we got up and requested breakfast at the table instead. That was sweet of them. Easy morning, was going to haul trash but that never happened. Kids did a lot of chores trying to earn tablet and computer time. Ashley and me took cookie money to Amanda and got more cookies. Had an issue with scheduling cookie booths but got that settled as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 14, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-14-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 23:51:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-14-2020/</guid>
      <description>Got up, no delay, still cold. Kids woke up to cards and candy from Lesa in their spots at the table. I had something in my spot too. I real quick had the kids sign their card to Lesa and we put her candy and cards in her spot. Everyone had something. Lesa left for work. I got the kids fed, drove them to school, and off to work I went.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 13, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-13-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 00:27:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-13-2020/</guid>
      <description>Got much colder, going to be single digits or worse overnight, worried about rabbits. Storm was supposed to hit us today but didn&amp;#8217;t, it went north of us instead. Kids stayed in truck until bus arrived. I got to work and just two of us there for the next hour. Ripped a couple of DVDs with tagged software and headed to SAIC. Spent the rest of the day there installing for EMI testing and have to go back in the morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 12, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-12-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 00:07:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-12-2020/</guid>
      <description>Rained nearly all day. Took kids to the bus stop per usual. Kids had a non-eventful day at school. Lesa worked and also just a normal day. Ditto for me, absolutely nothing happening. I did seem to get a lot of work done at least. Went to SAIC and installed latest development build and picked up several external drives to use for maps. Bought Mom/Son Nerf War tickets for Lesa and the boys from the Bedford Parks Department.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 11, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-11-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 00:05:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-11-2020/</guid>
      <description>Took kids to bus stop. Went into work for an hour and then headed to SAIC for software meeting. Got back to Scientia and worked the day until late and then left to pick up the kids. Got home and ate supper. Took Ashley to Bedford North Lawrence for the varsity game, they honored elementary school basketball players and cheerleaders at halftime by allowing them onto the court. She met up with Mrs Davis and I tried to hang back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 10, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-10-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 00:18:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-10-2020/</guid>
      <description>Back to work and school, thought I was going to go to SAIC but didn&amp;#8217;t, will be going in the morning. Kids wanted to go to school I think, I wonder if it&amp;#8217;s kind of comforting and relaxing for them, kind of like when Lesa and I feel like it&amp;#8217;s more peaceful at our desk than it is at home. I left at a reasonable time and picked up the kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 9, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-9-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 23:45:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-9-2020/</guid>
      <description>Cold and rainy all day and evening. We went to church, I was really tired and had a hard time staying away, Ashley had a nightmare and woke me up really early &amp;#8211; plus I probably stayed up too late as well, got to sit with Dillan and Lesa for once. Unloaded more cookies and took some reorders. We went to Bedford after church, ate lunch at Taco Bell, and went to CVS for Lesa&amp;#8217;s script.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 8, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-8-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 22:25:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-8-2020/</guid>
      <description>Woke up to snow on the ground. Super busy day. Took Ashley to Rural King to sell Girl Scout cookies at 10am, didn&amp;#8217;t sell a lot of cookies, would do much better at a grocery store I think. Came home and ate lunch and we all went to Dillan&amp;#8217;s basketball game, he is doing well, a little nervous and shooting the ball a bit hard and could use work dribbling but not bad for his first time playing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 7, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-7-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 02:00:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-7-2020/</guid>
      <description>Call at 5:40AM, school on a two-hour delay, let the kids sleep in a little, I wasn&amp;#8217;t able to fall back asleep. Lesa made it to work just fine, roads were clear, even the side roads, everyone I talked to had no issues and neither did I. Ran kids to daycare but they were understaffed and unable to drive the kids to school so back home we went. Later, back at the bus stop, the boys were playing and horsing around and just as the bus arrived Bruce face planted and busted his nose, lip and chin &amp;#8211; blood was gushing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 6, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-6-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 23:57:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-6-2020/</guid>
      <description>Waited for the kids to get on the bus per usual. Ashley went on a field trip to the State House, she had a lot of fun. Picked the kids up from daycare, stopped at Dollar General to restock truck candy. At dinner Dillan recalled the time he went to the State House and him and Ashley sort of compared notes (tried to outdo each other), nothing too bad and mostly good-natured, Ashley does that a lot but this time Dillan was a bit jealous.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 5, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-5-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 00:15:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-5-2020/</guid>
      <description>Rained all last night and day, sloppy muddy out. Took kids to bus for school. One of the first into work and didn&amp;#8217;t leave until the very last minute. Just barely got the kids! Probably close to breaking even on time, I&amp;#8217;ll figure it up tomorrow. Ashley brought home a paper about her hero &amp;#8211; it was me! I needed a shirt and tie for the dance this Friday, so I tried to take Dwyane and Bruce with me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 4, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-4-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 23:20:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-4-2020/</guid>
      <description>Bus, school, daycare for kids. Work for adults. Got off late trying to make up time for leaving early yesterday. Picked up kids near closing time and got home. No activities on the calendar and was going to take the boys and do something but didn&amp;#8217;t quite know what, so I opted to play Sorry with Dwyane and Bruce. They took showers so I played with one while the other was washing, Dillan and Ashley joined.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 3, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-3-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 22:59:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-3-2020/</guid>
      <description>Got kids up for school and fed, instead of the bus stop I drove them to school because Ashley had 3 boxes of Girl Scout cookies to hand out. Got off work early and picked up Ashley from school to go to the dermatologist. Barely! Nearly forgot and only just made it. Talked to Mr Hudson about the phone call we got from him last Friday concerning Bruce, nothing serious and no need to do anything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 2, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-2-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:04:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-2-2020/</guid>
      <description>Lesa had kids fed when I got up, fixed me breakfast too. We went to church, Family Sunday but I was lead in back and also lobby security so didn&amp;#8217;t get to spend time with family. Had Dillan help again with communion and he did good. Ashley had all her Cincinnati Christian Girl Scout cookie orders and got most of them handed out and paid for. Kaleena called and asked Ashley to come down to play, Ashley ate lunch and got Springville cookie orders ready for Monday, and then went down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 1, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-1-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 03:19:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-1-2020/</guid>
      <description>Slept in sort of, still got woke up by Bruce running through the house. My phone was just an expensive paperweight this morning, wouldn&amp;#8217;t power on or anything. Finally able to get it reset and it came on, not sure what that was all about but thought I was going to have to get another and redo everything, kind of scary how we depend on them things. Skipped breakfast for lunch instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 31, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--january-31-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 00:01:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--january-31-2020/</guid>
      <description>Took kids to bus, cold and wet out. Got donuts for work, it was payday Friday. Picked up kids from daycare. Lesa went grocery shopping. Message on the answering machine from Mr Hudson, Bruce was in his office for smacking another kid on the butt. Brought home sushi for Ashley to try, she liked some of it but not all, Dillan and Bruce tried some too and both of them liked they said, I wound up finishing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 30, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-30-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 22:51:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-30-2020/</guid>
      <description>Bus stop, school, daycare for kids. Ashley wore one of the new outfits Lesa bought her. Lesa worked all day. I worked all day in Bloomington. Everyone is still healthy, just one more day to make an entire week, first time in three weeks. Picked kids up and Lesa already had supper ready. Lesa got Ashley to her Girl Scout meeting. I took Dillan to his basketball practice and then rushed to pick Ashley up and get back in time before practice ended, it rained most of the day and the roads were slick but I did okay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 29, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-29-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 23:52:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-29-2020/</guid>
      <description>Got kids ready for school, breakfast of mostly left-over pancakes from yesterday&amp;#8217;s Bob Evan&amp;#8217;s meal, shipped them off to school on the bus. Headed to work. Lesa seemed to have a better day then she had yesterday while I felt blah all day. Had military big-wigs in the shop, everyone kind of hyper and anal about appearances, etc. Took off about 4:30p and left to get kids. Picked them up and no sooner were we in the truck when Dillan and Dwyane started fighting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 28, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-28-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 23:22:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-28-2020/</guid>
      <description>Repeat of yesterday, took kids to bus stop, they went to school, everyone seems healthy, Bruce has a slight cough. I went to the Urologist again only this time I really did have an appointment, no issues, set appointment for next year, looking like enlarged prostate and elevated PSA is normal for me, Lesa and I both relieved no cancer for the moment. Lesa also went to see the doctor, didn&amp;#8217;t say why, she said routine stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 27, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-27-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 22:24:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-27-2020/</guid>
      <description>Checked everyone&amp;#8217;s temps this morning, everyone okay to go to school, Bruce had a nose bleed getting ready, Lesa probably the sickest but she went to work too. I went to the Urologist in Bloomington, realized my appointment is for tomorrow, and drove all the way back to Bedford and worked at SAIC all day. Texted with Lesa, she had a rough day and didn&amp;#8217;t feel very well. I thought I was going to get sick myself a couple of times, didn&amp;#8217;t finish my coffee or eat breakfast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 26, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-26-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 01:56:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-26-2020/</guid>
      <description>Got up, took Ashley, Dwyane and Bruce to church, Serving Deacon, traded home bound communion duties, didn&amp;#8217;t want to be the reason some old person got sick. Ashley made a lot of cookie sales at church. When we got back home I made everyone lunch, and then I made everyone take naps, even though they didn&amp;#8217;t want to everyone fell asleep right away and slept awhile. Lesa and Dillan are feeling better but no where near 100% yet, worried he&amp;#8217;ll still be sick in the morning and don&amp;#8217;t have a plan for that yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 25, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-25-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 00:46:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-25-2020/</guid>
      <description>Got up and took care of everyone, Lesa sick, Dillan sick, Bruce sick, Dwyane half sick, Ashley okay and a big help! Missed the Beekeeping Seminar I was going to attend with Ken. Missed Dillan&amp;#8217;s first Courts for Christ basketball game. Made lunch. Did dishes. Did laundry. Made it to Ashley&amp;#8217;s first cookie booth, her share was 40 boxes sold! Made supper. Kids took showers. Played Sorry with boys and Lesa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 24, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-24-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 00:28:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-24-2020/</guid>
      <description>All kids went to school, took them off to the bus stop and saw them off then headed to work. Lesa worked as well. Got a call at 10:30am, Dillan not feeling well and running a fever! F*ck! Can&amp;#8217;t catch a break! Lesa had a meeting and had to be at work, I had lunch at noon and it was mandatory as well. Rushed to Springville Elementary, in the rain, and got Dillan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 23, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-23-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:52:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-23-2020/</guid>
      <description>Bruce slept the night through! No fever! Must have broke sometime during the night. Took the other three to the bus stop, and went to work. Lesa stayed home and watched Bruce. He&amp;#8217;ll go to school tomorrow unless something happens overnight. I went to Dr Thompson&amp;#8217;s office at 10am, fasted the entire time, supposed to just be lab work, waited 40 minutes and still didn&amp;#8217;t have my blood drawn, got mad and told them I&amp;#8217;d reschedule and call them later, and left.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 22, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-22-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 11:35:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-22-2020/</guid>
      <description>Bruce had a horrible night, he came out absolutely terrified, was starring at something no one else could see, and he was very confused. After 15-20 minutes I finally got him calmed down enough to where he could tell me what was wrong: a dinosaur came and it ate me and was after him. Slept with him on the couch for awhile, and finally got him settled and in his bed around 3:30am.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 21, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-21-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:19:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-21-2020/</guid>
      <description>More sickness! Dwyane 101° something and felt bad. Bruce 103.7° and Ibuprofen barely reduced it. Bruce got up multiple times last night. Lesa had to be at work so I took off to watch the boys. Took Dillan and Ashley to the bus stop and saw them off, went to Springville Store and got some Sprite and headed home. Tried to do so work but Bruce dry heaved half the morning, poor guy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 20, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-20-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:16:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-20-2020/</guid>
      <description>Martin Luther King Junior Day and Lesa and I had off. The kids had school to make up a snow day so we were kid-free. I got up and got kids ready for school and took them to the bus stop. I went back to bed and slept all morning! Got up, we took showers, and went to Bloomington for lunch. We went to Asuka Japanese Steakhouse, Sushi &amp;amp; Noodles and did the Hibachi, first time experience for us, we had steak and shrimp with fried rice, and soup prior.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 19, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-19-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:01:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-19-2020/</guid>
      <description>Church, I taught in Junior Church as well. Kids glad I was there and the boys hung out with me. They love us so much it&amp;#8217;s hard to fathom sometimes. After church, Shane Schroyer came out and checked our furnace, it was acting kind of odd a few weeks ago but seems to be okay. Bruce and then Dillan hung out with us to watch. After Shane left we had lunch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 18, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-18-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2020 23:09:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-18-2020/</guid>
      <description>Slept in and a lazy morning, kids did some chores and workbooks to get tablet, computer, or Wii time. A lot of looking over the other&amp;#8217;s shoulder to see what the other was up to. After lunch we went to the library and saw the McCluskey&amp;#8217;s. I threw a fit over the books Dillan tends to get before we left and he picked two that were more age appropriate but I doubt he&amp;#8217;ll read them, will probably just backfire on me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 17, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-17-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2020 01:43:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-17-2020/</guid>
      <description>Friday! Took kids to bus stop. Lesa and I had a date night and we both took off a little bit early from work. I picked up the kids and we headed to Bloomington. Todd and Paulette Davidson watched the kids for us so we could go out for dinner. It was awesome. We went to Red Lobster, or as Bruce called it, Red Hamsters. Had a fantastic dinner and then we went to the mall and walked around a bit, talked, joked about being the old people walking the mall for exercise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 16, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-16-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 22:35:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-16-2020/</guid>
      <description>Bus stop, school, and daycare for the kids. Work and more work for the adults. Waited until last minute before leaving to get the kids. Lesa had supper ready per usual when we got home. Girl Scout meeting was canceled. I took Dillan to his first Courts for Christ basketball practice. Ashley went with, Lesa encouraged it. Lesa stayed home with boys doing I know not what. Dillan did okay for not having really played before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 15, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-15-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 22:18:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-15-2020/</guid>
      <description>Took kids to bus stop. Lesa and I both worked. Worked a little over but not much. Picked up kids, almost sorry I did, little pills like usual. I&amp;#8217;m not really sorry of course, they are blessings but there are those times as I&amp;#8217;m sure every parent knows. Got home, no where to go tonight, thank goodness! Stayed home, watched TV, took showers and baths, did homework, the usual boring stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 14, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-14-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 23:08:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-14-2020/</guid>
      <description>Dropped kids at bus stop, Lesa and I both worked. Dillan blew off career day, I suggested he draw some lines on paper and say he was going to be a criminal, he didn&amp;#8217;t like that so much. I worked until last minute and then left to get kids from daycare. No activities scheduled so kids watched an hour of TV. Ashley and me read some of the Bible and Dillan was listening in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 13, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-13-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 23:47:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-13-2020/</guid>
      <description>Lesa worked. I took all four kids to the dentist first thing in the morning, before school started even. Dillan needs to brush better lower front and upper back. Ashley, Dwyane, and Bruce need to brush better along gum lines. Dentist didn&amp;#8217;t want to remove spacer and I&amp;#8217;m not sure what we&amp;#8217;re going to do yet. Took them to school afterward and then went to work myself. Lesa picked up the kids, I was at SAIC by then.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 12, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-12-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 22:27:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-12-2020/</guid>
      <description>Got up, took kids to church with me, Lesa stayed home. I was roaming deacon and Dillan roamed with me, he also shadowed/helped me serve communion in back. We kept the kids inside due to the rain, the ground is really saturated and everything is muddy and we didn&amp;#8217;t feel like dealing with the mess of four kids. Not sure having them inside was any better &amp;#8211; lots of fighting and aggravating each other, and us, per usual.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 11, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-11-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 02:19:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-11-2020/</guid>
      <description>Got up at 8a, got kids breakfast and dressed, and had them out the door by 9a. Went to the Springville Basketball Tournament, Ashley was a cheerleader, rest of us watched. We lost, and probably the last game for forever since they&amp;#8217;re shutting down the school. Went to Steak &amp;#8216;n&amp;#8217; Shake and had lunch with shakes to go. Tried to nap, kids did homework and chores depending on the kid. Lesa played Monopoly with the boys and I played Trouble with Ashley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 10, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-10-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 23:09:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-10-2020/</guid>
      <description>Friday, it&amp;#8217;s been an exhausting week! Dropped off kids at bus stop and went into work. All of them seemed a little bit iffy except for Dillan, expected to get a call any time to come get one of them but they made it through the day. Got picked up from school by daycare. Lesa went grocery shopping and then picked up the kids on her way home. I went to the doctor&amp;#8217;s office after work for a six month followup and all seems well, need to drink more water and exercise more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 9, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-9-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 23:54:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-9-2020/</guid>
      <description>Lesa watching sick kids, probably last day, they seem to be doing better. Took Dillan and Dwyane to bus stop. Coming back Dillan and Dwyane walked home from bus stop. Lesa and kids weren&amp;#8217;t getting along, especially Ashley. Issues, I got calls from Ashley saying Mommy was being mean, got calls from Lesa saying Ashley being mean, got another call from Ashley saying Lesa locked her out of the house, and another saying Lesa was following her everywhere with a video camera, f*ck my life!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 8, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-8-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 00:15:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-8-2020/</guid>
      <description>My day to take care of the sick kids again, got Dillan and Dwyane to the bus just fine. Let Ashley and Bruce sleep in late and when they did wake up I delivered software to SAIC, went to Dollar General to get some Gatorade for Bruce, and stopped by daycare and paid them. Got home, they didn&amp;#8217;t want breakfast, let them watch TV. Bruce threw up watching TV and got some on him and his blanket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 7, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-7-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 23:50:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-7-2020/</guid>
      <description>I worked today. Took Dillan and Dwyane to the bus stop. Lesa stayed home with Ashley and Bruce. I forgot my phone, bad day for that, school called to let us know our kids were missing, super busy at work and needed to make lots of calls and had to borrow phones. Bruce threw up. Lesa stressed. Ashley full of drama. Daycare wanted doctor releases. Lesa had to call my boss to get a hold of me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 6, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-6-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:26:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-6-2020/</guid>
      <description>Dillan woke us shortly after 2:00am and told us Bruce was screaming and crying. Turns out he was running a pretty high fever of 102.9°F. He&amp;#8217;s sick! Gave him some Ibuprofen to help him out. Wound up spending the night with him on the couch. Lesa HAD to be at work since all the students returned today so I was the lucky person to stay home with him. We watched movies and cat-napped.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 5, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-5-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 00:55:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-5-2020/</guid>
      <description>Church, Family Sunday, combined Sunday School, Dillan still at Gabe&amp;#8217;s and didn&amp;#8217;t go to church with us. Kids played, and we had Dillan home by two. Went to Walmart and let the kids get some toys or in Ashley&amp;#8217;s case some toys and crafts, with their Christmas money and gift cards. Thirty dollars each and they enjoyed even if we didn&amp;#8217;t so much. Got home and kids played rest of the afternoon, Bruce was exercising his imagination some which was refreshing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 4, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-4-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 00:30:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-4-2020/</guid>
      <description>Kids woke us of course. Fought with each other of course. Drove us crazy of course. Wouldn&amp;#8217;t listen to us of course. Talked back to us of course. Boys played. Ashley played. Lesa worked. I tried to sleep. Lesa fixed up Ashley&amp;#8217;s Girl Scout vest. I took Dillan to Dunham&amp;#8217;s Sports and bought him basketball shoes, shorts, pants and jacket, protector, and a basketball (to be shared), he starts basketball practice with Courts for Christ next week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 3, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-3-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2020 01:44:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-3-2020/</guid>
      <description>Work and daycare. Dropped kids off and headed to work. Lesa and I texted back-and-forth on how to handle Ashley&amp;#8217;s Cookie Rally at Stalker. Ended up Lesa went grocery shopping and she picked up a couple of pizzas from Springville Store while I picked up the kids from daycare, I needed to get gas so did that first. Jessica said she had issues with Bruce but the other kids did okay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 2, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-2-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 01:04:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-2-2020/</guid>
      <description>Lesa worked, daycare closed, I took the day off. Ashley woke me up and said she heard my phone beeping and her stomach hurt from being so hungry. Yeah, drama in the morning. Anyway, my phone had several texts from Lesa, her window was down and wouldn&amp;#8217;t roll up and she had about $600 worth of parking permits plus she kind of needed her Jeep. So I pulled the window motor from the spare Jeep, got the kids fed and dressed, and headed to her work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 1, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-1-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 23:36:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-1-2020/</guid>
      <description>Kids woke us up, I sent them to their rooms and told them to be quiet. Went back to bed and to sleep. Lesa got up and kept things quiet. I slept until 10am! Longest in almost 6 years unless sick. It was awesome. Lesa made me coffee which was nice. I played Battleship with Ashley, then Dwyane. Took Dwyane to Mrs Dillman&amp;#8217;s house, her grandson Jay invited Dwyane to spend the night and go to Urban Air with them, it&amp;#8217;s his first sleepover, I think he&amp;#8217;s ready and will be okay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 31, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--december-31-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 02:01:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--december-31-2019/</guid>
      <description>New Year&amp;#8217;s Eve. Worked, both of us. Lesa got off early and got the place cleaned up. I worked a full day and picked up kids. Got home and we all went into overdrive cleaning and picking up, well maybe not Bruce. Ken and Cassie Tussey, Emma and Woodrow came over to eat pizza, and they brought venison sausage with them! We played several games of euchre while kids played and ultimately watched TV.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 30, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-30-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 23:45:40 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-30-2019/</guid>
      <description>New Year&amp;#8217;s Eve Eve. Work and daycare, both sucked. Picked kids up and got an earful about the kids&amp;#8217; behavior. Dillan and Ashley fighting over a chair, Ashley scratched and drew blood, Dillan pinched and caused a welt, both told to sit and Dillan went off about how he hates it at daycare and started kicking a chair around. Bruce mouthed off at Annetta and got a timeout for that. Ashley and Dwyane fighting over a pillow, Dwyane throwing it in the bathroom and Ashley hitting him for doing it, multiple times, each trying to outdo the other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 29, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-29-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 23:18:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-29-2019/</guid>
      <description>Skipped church, slept in, Lesa and kids tired, me too I guess. I never even got dressed. Boys did so they could play outside. I flew my drone. Ashley made necklaces and bracelets and Lesa and I helped her get sewing machine working. Lesa wrestled with Bruce and he had lots of fun. Kids did their best to clean out my truck but didn&amp;#8217;t do a very good job, mostly fought among themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 28, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-28-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 00:27:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-28-2019/</guid>
      <description>Easy morning, got woke by kids, but not too early. Kids played with toys but Lesa had to put them outside, they were just too rowdy. She packed some sandwiches and at noon we headed to Sarah and Kaleigh&amp;#8217;s for the Williams Christmas. Two hours later we arrived, right on time. Becky and Maelee and boys already there, my parents and brother came shortly after. Kids had a great time, we had a good time too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 27, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-27-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 00:01:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-27-2019/</guid>
      <description>Took kids to daycare, had to yell at them to get them ready, not the usual yelling but really yell, they just don&amp;#8217;t want to do anything but play. Sorry to say this but I was kind of relieved to be at work. Lesa worked too but she got off early and went to CVS and grocery shopping before heading home. I left on time and picked up the kids. They rode bikes until dark and we watched MIB International while eating pizza.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 26, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-26-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 23:37:40 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-26-2019/</guid>
      <description>I got to sleep in, Bruce (Lesa) made me breakfast in bed. Kids got to play all day. Helped Ashley with her bracelet braider, helped Bruce with his puzzle, Dillan did fine with his car, and finally got to fly my drone. Dillan went to Gabe&amp;#8217;s for awhile, boys got their tablets, Ashley got my phone and her tablet, Dwyane danced and Bruce joined in. It was a pretty awesome day except for the kids fighting and bickering and complaining.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 25, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-25-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 22:57:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-25-2019/</guid>
      <description>Christmas Day! Ashley got up at 4:00am, woke up Dillan at 4:30am, woke me up at 5:00am, I told her come back at 7:00am, and she did. Got up, Santa had visited, stockings were full too. Let the kids play all morning. Left for Indy and the Dellinger Christmas at noon, stopped at McDonald&amp;#8217;s on way, kids played with their cousins and had such fun. I haven&amp;#8217;t had much contact with my birth mom&amp;#8217;s side over the years but I&amp;#8217;m glad they accept the kids the way they do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 24, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-24-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 01:33:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-24-2019/</guid>
      <description>Kids on break, we both took off, kids up way too early, excited as all get out. Lesa went to Dollar General and Walmart to get last minute stuff for Christmas. When she returned it was my turn. Asked kids if they wanted to go and Ashley and Dwyane said yes, I made Dillan and Bruce go anyway. I was trying to allow Lesa some time to herself. We went to Bed, Bath and Beyond and Kay Jewelers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 23, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-23-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 23:20:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-23-2019/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217;s Christmas Eve Eve. Kids on Christmas Break, both Lesa and I had to work, I dropped boys off at daycare and Ashley went to work with me to play with Addie, my bosses daughter. There&amp;#8217;s a 5-year age gap there and Ashley got bored pretty quickly but she did good and made sure she was a friend to Addie. At noon I was hoping to leave, not able to, so stopped at Taco Bell and drove Ashley to daycare then came back to work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 22, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-22-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 23:01:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-22-2019/</guid>
      <description>Family Church, Christmas Sunday, no evening service, short service and out earlier than usual. Kids have absolutely lost their minds. It was a beautiful afternoon and the kids insisted on tearing the house up, running, around like crazy, but when we asked them to go outside they said no. Then they started picking and fighting with each other, started to actually try and hurt each other, and had to try and put a stop to that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 21, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-21-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 01:10:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-21-2019/</guid>
      <description>Sort of slept in, here the pitter-patter of feet, Lesa already up, figured she&amp;#8217;d be frustrated already so I got up. Lesa made me coffee, Ashley and Bruce snuggled with me. Lazy morning for me. After lunch, I hauled trash with Ashley and Bruce, Lesa and Dillan helped load. From trash we went to Lowe&amp;#8217;s and got a new garbage disposal and some cabinet rails rear mounts. Then I bought them Frosties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 20, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-20-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 00:37:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-20-2019/</guid>
      <description>School, daycare, work. Lesa had a long rough day of moving and network being out &amp;#8211; per usual. I had an okay workday but couldn&amp;#8217;t wait to get out of there. Kids had a fun day of partying at school, Polar Express day where they wore their pajamas and watched the movie, a scavenger hunt, and other festivities to kick off Christmas Break. I left work at 3:30pm and went to get kids, picked up a card Daniel sent to our PO Box, picked up Papa John&amp;#8217;s pizza, and filled my tank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 19, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-19-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 23:44:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-19-2019/</guid>
      <description>Lesa and I both worked full days. The kids went to school, they kids had their Christmas parties and gift exchanges and the excitement was high all day, by all accounts they had a great time. Mrs Malone and Mrs Willis blew up our phones with text messages and photos. More sledding, boys also played in the woods, none of them had gloves on! Their hands were red and will probably be chapped.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 18, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-18-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 23:05:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-18-2019/</guid>
      <description>Took kids to school, Lesa had off, I worked a normal day. Lesa got 50-some gifts wrapped and under the tree and she was also able to get to CVS for Dillan and Dwyane&amp;#8217;s medicine. Kids were super-excited when they got home. Bruce is the most excited and wants to open gifts now, hope he&amp;#8217;s not disappointed in what he gets for Christmas. Boys sledded before supper, Ashley read almost two hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 17, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-17-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 23:40:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-17-2019/</guid>
      <description>Call at 5:50am saying NLCS on a 2-hr delay. Call at 7:40am saying NLCS now closed. Lesa at work. I took kids to daycare and went to work too. Lesa picked up Dillan and Dwyane from daycare and took them to the doctor. They both had ear aches and Dillan had excess ear wax built up that the doctor removed. Lesa went to CVS and they didn&amp;#8217;t have scripts ready so she got some groceries and went back, still not ready!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 16, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-16-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 23:40:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-16-2019/</guid>
      <description>No closing, no two hour delay, just school per usual, roads wet but fine, kids were really disappointed. Kids wore Christmas sweaters today. Worked late. Picked up kids last minute, rushed home, ate dinner, and kids changed into pajamas for the Springville Elementary Christmas Sing-A-Long. Off we went, the boys classes were first, followed by the older kids. They all did good and sang. It was short but enjoyable. Got home early enough to watch TV, they watched The Santa Claus 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 15, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-15-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:19:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-15-2019/</guid>
      <description>Up until 4am doing the meditation, didn&amp;#8217;t fall asleep until an hour later, woke up when Lesa got up at 6a, then got woke up by kids at 7:30a. Gave the communion meditation, got a lot of positive feedback. Delivered communion to a home bound lady that made an impression on Ashley because Ashley prayed for her at lunch. Dillan went down to Gabe&amp;#8217;s, Lesa went to Walmart and Rural King, Ashley and Dwyane played in her room, Bruce played on Wii Console, and I actually got to nap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 14, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-14-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:34:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-14-2019/</guid>
      <description>Tried to sleep in, honest. Was awakened by Ashley and Bruce standing next to my side of the bed, in the dark, and they said: It&amp;#8217;s an emergency. Dwyane is bleeding from his eye. And I was awake just like that. So, they were chasing each other, and Dwyane tripped over some pillows, and hit his eye on Bruce&amp;#8217;s toy box. Goose egg on the forehead above his eyebrow, and a ¼&amp;#8221; cut on his eye lid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 13, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-13-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 01:03:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-13-2019/</guid>
      <description>School, work, daycare. Worked later, picked up kids later, stopped by bank on the way. Lesa grocery shopped. Ate pizza and went to Santa House, arrived at 6pm, got Sleigh 14 at 8:45pm, so we waited at the old bath house, watched A Charlie Brown Christmas followed by Polar Express 3D version. That put us at 8:30pm, everyone took a bathroom break, then off to Santa and Mrs Claus&amp;#8217; house. Ashley, Dwyane, and Bruce told Santa what they wanted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 12, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-12-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 23:11:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-12-2019/</guid>
      <description>Work and school, had a frustrating day, glad it&amp;#8217;s over. Since we were going to Walmart, I thought it might save time if I just picked Lesa up, then the kids, then get a bite to eat, then Walmart. Asian Pearl, everyone got stuff they liked, it was a hit with the kids. Went to Walmart after, spent $355 dollars on a coat, new jammies for all the kids, and gift cards for Christmas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 11, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-11-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 00:34:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-11-2019/</guid>
      <description>Dropped kids at school, headed to SAIC to pick up a couple of SSD drives for video archiving. Went to Bloomington and worked there until 3pm and then headed back to SAIC for another drive for maps. Have to get some Afghanistan maps delivered tomorrow or Friday. Met Lesa at TK Constructions model home in Bedford and did a walk-through &amp;#8211; without kids &amp;#8211; and liked what we saw. I picked up kids from daycare afterward and Lesa went home and started supper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 10, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-10-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 23:02:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-10-2019/</guid>
      <description>School, daycare, work, same old, same old. Home game against Dollens Elementary, it&amp;#8217;s the last game of the season, the girls lost and the boys won. Ashley said there are playoff games on January 7th at BNL but nothing official yet. Ashley said she felt sick when I got there but I told her it was the last game and she should stick it out so she did. Dwyane got to wear the hornet mascot suit again, he had a good time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 9, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-9-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 22:49:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-9-2019/</guid>
      <description>School, daycare, and work. Worked until last minute, went to the bank, barely made it to daycare in time to pick up the kids. Rained all day but temperatures were decent. Scout pack meeting tonight and I signed up for grapes, Lesa stopped by the store on her way home to get some. Supper was ready when kids and me got home, we ate, and headed to the pack meeting. Dwyane had snacks and Bruce was color guard; lots of awards, mostly popcorn related; last meeting of the year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 8, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-8-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 22:19:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-8-2019/</guid>
      <description>Church, deacon in back. After lunch Lesa ran Christmas at the Zoo money to Amanda. I felt sick so tried to nap but butt hole neighbor was shooting. Dillan went down to Gabe&amp;#8217;s and Ashley went to Kaleena&amp;#8217;s. Boys played inside/outside. I put new straw and some Timothy hay in the rabbit hutch for Ashley. Kids got home at 5:00p and I turned on Indiana Jones, then they watched another right after.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 7, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-7-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 23:58:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-7-2019/</guid>
      <description>Slept until 8am, surprised at that. Stopped by PO Box and picked up another letter from Daniel om my way to take the kids to get hair cuts at Fantastic Sams. The boys wanted their hair cut short so we did the #4 on top and #2 on side summer cut. Ashley wanted bangs, stylist checked and said it wouldn&amp;#8217;t work very well, so she got her ends trimmed as originally planned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 6, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-6-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 23:28:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-6-2019/</guid>
      <description>School, daycare, work. Ashley sat in RTI room, not sure what that is. Missed lunch with the teacher. She earned the honor but had to forfeit it due to her bad behavior the other day. Kids were talking about her all day and that bothered her &amp;#8211; I say good. Picked up the kids from daycare, went home and we waited for Lesa to get home from work and grocery shopping, helped her carry in and put up, then we all went to the Scientia Christmas party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 5, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-5-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 23:05:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-5-2019/</guid>
      <description>Work and school. Had a map meeting at 11:00am to discuss maps and map resources and didn&amp;#8217;t get out until 2:00pm! Lesa went to the dentist, got a clean and polish, no cavities. I got a text from Mrs Davis saying Ashley was in trouble and would have to sit out a game tonight, and that Mr Hudson would be calling me about it. Saw where I had a missed Springville call and called him back, he was in a meeting and would get back to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 4, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-4-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 00:19:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-4-2019/</guid>
      <description>School and work. Picked up kids from daycare. Only thing planned was Wheeler Mission presentation at Cincinnati Christian Church and I opted not to go. The kids are so tired as are we. Ashley had a total meltdown after getting sent to bed early for talking back to me. Everyone hates her and she hates her life. Zaida at school is being mean, Lesa and me don&amp;#8217;t love her and are being mean, and she wants to see her Grandpa David and Cousin Eve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 3, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-3-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 00:41:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-3-2019/</guid>
      <description>Ashley had a nightmare, crawled into bed between us, I tucked her back into her bed. Work and school again. Left in time to take Ashley to an away game at Stalker. All the boys went to daycare and Lesa picked them up from there. I was really worried Lesa would be stressed when when got home but she didn&amp;#8217;t seem to be. Looked like the boys played the Wii. By the time Ashley and I got home everyone else had already eaten supper so we ate together by ourselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 2, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-2-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:02:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-2-2019/</guid>
      <description>Back to work and school. We suffered today. I picked up the mail from the PO Box, another letter from Daniel. Same old, same old. How he&amp;#8217;s sorry, how he loves the kids so much, how he wishes the kids would forgive him and write back. He pretends he cares about the kids, pretends to be sorry, but in reality his letters are all about him. We see typical addict behavior and mentality and we suspect the sudden burst of letters has to do with a program of some sort and he&amp;#8217;s hoping to gain an early release or something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 1, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-1-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 23:27:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-1-2019/</guid>
      <description>Planned on hunting, last day of season. Lesa wanted me to stay in to help with kids so I did. We went to church, Family Sunday, and basically chilled the afternoon away. Chilled as in Lesa and I didn&amp;#8217;t go anywhere or do much work. Lesa always works so that doesn&amp;#8217;t count. She did play a board game with the kids though, except Dillan who went to Gabe&amp;#8217;s. Kaleena was going to come down but not sure what happened there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 30, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-30-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 22:52:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-30-2019/</guid>
      <description>Williams Thanksgiving today. Nasty rainy day all day. Lesa had a lot of cooking going on so I took the kids to Starbucks to get hot chocolate and mostly to get then out of her hair. Then we went to Walmart and got a couple of items Lesa needed like dinner rolls and celery. Skipped the donuts even though it was tempting. First to show was Sarah and Kaleigh followed by Becky and kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 29, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-29-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 23:40:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-29-2019/</guid>
      <description>Got up before daylight and went deer hunting, Didn&amp;#8217;t see anything. Got in and Lesa frustrated with kids but trying hard. Ashley busy cleaning her room and making it safe for Maelee. Boys have a mess absolutely everywhere. Spent part of the day cleaning up the house, yard and deck. After lunch Lesa went grocery shopping and kids got tablets for the chores they did. Lesa got home with the ingredients we needed to make deserts for tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 28, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-28-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 00:16:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-28-2019/</guid>
      <description>Slept in, sort of. Had to get up to go to Avery and Emily&amp;#8217;s for Thanksgiving. Kids super excited to see their cousins and played with them all day. Lesa and I hung with family and everyone had a good dinner. Hate the drive to Indy now-a-days but we made good time coming and going. The kids rode bikes when we got home, it was near dark but we let them burn off the energy anyway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 27, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-27-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 00:04:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-27-2019/</guid>
      <description>Let the kids sleep an extra hour since no school. Took them to daycare. Lesa stayed home and cleaned house. I went to work, wasn&amp;#8217;t too late. Power flickered on and off at work and finally stayed off, estimate to fix was 11pm. Most everyone went home, me included. Lesa didn&amp;#8217;t want me to pick up kids yet so I didn&amp;#8217;t. Home and hour and power out here too. Outage map said estimate on getting service restored 1:20am so I got the generator going, hooked up the TV and a light, and while I was getting a space heater the electricity came back on!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 26, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-26-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 01:01:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-26-2019/</guid>
      <description>Lesa tossed and turned and coughed all night long and kept us both up. She&amp;#8217;s sick. Hope I don&amp;#8217;t get sick! Got up, got kids ready, took them to school. They acted like they were on vacation already and didn&amp;#8217;t want to get ready. Dillan spent 20 minutes in the shower that was supposed to be a rinse-off shower. Anyway, got them to school. Put Ashley&amp;#8217;s cheerleader bow in her hair in the school parking lot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 25, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-25-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 23:37:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-25-2019/</guid>
      <description>Lesa on vacation all week, cleaning and prepping for Thanksgiving. I get to work. Kids had school so I got them up and ready and dropped them off. Ashley and Dwyane had a home game against Lincoln and I left work a few minutes early to go. Girls lost but the boys game was the best elementary school game ever. The crowd thought so too. Very exciting and a lot of fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 24, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-24-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 21:48:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-24-2019/</guid>
      <description>Was going to skip church and go deer hunting but Lesa would have had a rough time getting kids ready and there so I went with. Filled in as front deacon. I was messing around with Dillan during the sermon &amp;#8211; again, and Lesa got mad at us &amp;#8211; again. Dillan was missing homework again, got it online, and made him do it, he had a fit. Afterward he finished he went to Gabe&amp;#8217;s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 23, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-23-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 00:49:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-23-2019/</guid>
      <description>Went out deer hunting this morning, rained the entire time. Didn&amp;#8217;t see a thing but I heard some turkeys. Was supposed to pick up Bruce from Corbin&amp;#8217;s house around noon, then one or two, then they went to Bloomington, and I finally picked him up about three-thirty. They played X-Box, went to Captain D&amp;#8217;s for dinner, had meatloaf sandwiches for breakfast and toasted PBJs for lunch, stayed up late and slept in late.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 22, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-22-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 23:43:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-22-2019/</guid>
      <description>Friday! School, daycare, work. Left early, picked up kids, got a couple hours hunting in. Bruce rode the bus home with Corbin, Grady rides the same bus, because Bruce is spending the night at Corbin&amp;#8217;s. He&amp;#8217;s been excited all week and apparently he&amp;#8217;s a big kid now &amp;#8211; at least he&amp;#8217;s been acting like it. Emma was supposed to spend the night, came over awhile and did crafts with Ashley, they made a huge mess of the glitter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 21, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-21-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 00:21:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-21-2019/</guid>
      <description>School and work, school and work. Left early, picked up Ashley as a car-rider, daycare got the boys. Took Ashley to St. Vincent to cheer for the basketball games, we were early so hung out in the gym until things picked up. Meanwhile, Lesa picked up the boys. Girls team won their game 23 to 19. We left early because Ashley said she had a headache and wanted to go. When we left the boys were losing by 8 or 10 points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 20, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-20-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 21:04:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-20-2019/</guid>
      <description>Kids school, Lesa and me went to work. Dropped off Girl Scout destined for daycare before work. Got another letter from Daniel dated November 12 and scanned and added it to site. Picked up kids from daycare. Talked to Annetta and Jessica for quite awhile about school closings. Ashley told them we&amp;#8217;re going to go to a different school so naturally they were wondering about our kids. Dillan told me I was a good dad, better than his birth dad, because I love and take care of him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 19, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-19-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 23:00:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-19-2019/</guid>
      <description>School and work, rained all day, slow-ish day for me, not sure about Lesa. Left at 4:30 and got the kids on the late side but I don&amp;#8217;t think they noticed &amp;#8211; they were watching TV. Got home and no place to go! Checked rabbits with Ashley, boys played, a little bit of homework with Lesa, Ashley read for an hour and then Maelee-proofed her room for Thanksgiving. Boys took baths, Dillan a shower.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 18, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-18-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:52:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-18-2019/</guid>
      <description>School and work. Kids already excited for Thanksgiving, they thought they got off this week. Gave myself a haircut. Went to SAIC and worked the afternoon. Got to daycare earlier than usual, took the kids to Dollar General and restocked the truck candy supply. Ate supper, boys didn&amp;#8217;t want to go to Cub Scouts, made them anyway, they had a lot of fun, and announced on the way home they loved Scouts and want to keep going.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 17, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-17-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2019 23:32:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-17-2019/</guid>
      <description>Took kids to church, Lesa stayed home, passed out a lot of Girl Scout candy orders, worked in Junior Church, got Bruce to do motions with me but not Dwyane. Ashley is a leader at church and very smart with the lessons. Ashley&amp;#8217;s Girl Scout trip to WonderLab didn&amp;#8217;t materialize, leaders sort of nixed it as too much activity for one weekend. Dillan got home about 1:30pm. We all went to Rural King and got straw for the rabbits bedding and some chicken feed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 16, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-16-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 22:15:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-16-2019/</guid>
      <description>Up before everyone, opening day deer season, out before light, then in at 11a, and out again at 3p until dark. Didn&amp;#8217;t see a thing other than squirrels! Ashley had a Girl Scout ecology event in Hoosier National Forest on opening day of all day! That scares me to death! She climbed the fire tower. That scares me to death too! She came back to us by the grace of God.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 15, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-15-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 23:26:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-15-2019/</guid>
      <description>Work and school. I had to go to SAIC to deliver the latest and greatest OS and hoped to be there by 4p but that wasn&amp;#8217;t going to happen so I figured early Monday morning. Stopped and picked up the kids. Went ahead and drove to SAIC and was able to get a pass in, had to sign to get all the kids in, and made my delivery. Kids thought it was awesome cool to see all the military gear and equipment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 14, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-14-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 22:27:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-14-2019/</guid>
      <description>Lesa working from home today, she has a 1:00 dentist appointment and Dillan and Ashley have eye exams. I worked at Scientia. Got off and I went straight to the Bedford North Lawrence (BNL) Professional Arts Center (PAC). I was number 37 to speak and had a minute to do so. Stood in front of 500+ people plus live stream audience and said my say on keeping Springville Elementary open. Not my usual evening activity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 13, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-13-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 23:26:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-13-2019/</guid>
      <description>School open, took kids. Went to work myself. Lesa worked as well. Non-eventful work and school day. Lesa picked up Ashley after her cheerleading practice. I picked up the boys. Slow evening but got an email from Jerry Hill concerning the school closings, particularly Springville Elementary. Called him and he wants me to speak at the public input session tomorrow night at the BNL PAC center. He also told Lesa a couple of weeks ago I should run for school board.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 12, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-12-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 22:53:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-12-2019/</guid>
      <description>School canceled. Lesa went in an hour late. I stayed home and kept the kids with me, didn&amp;#8217;t have it in me to drop them off at daycare. Ashley mostly watched TV and played with a doll, the boys played outside in the snow. Bruce came in and cried because his feet got too cold, got him warmed up, and put my heavy wool socks on him. Hot chocolate and some vegetable soup got them all warmed up again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 11, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-11-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 23:51:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-11-2019/</guid>
      <description>Veteran&amp;#8217;s Day, I have off! Got up early though to take kids to school. Lesa went to work. Went to Johnson&amp;#8217;s house, helped Ross move roll-top desk, loaded mower and cart and brought home. Went back for treadmill and opted not, helped him load in his truck. They gave us a 42&amp;#8243; plasma TV and a chest freezer. Went to kids&amp;#8217; Veteran&amp;#8217;s Day Program, I&amp;#8217;m proud of them and our school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 10, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-10-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 23:28:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-10-2019/</guid>
      <description>Church, Deacon in Back and Lobby Security. Afterward, we hooked up trailer and loaded bikes, got gas, and went to Paul and Andrea&amp;#8217;s for lunch with the Johnsons. Beautiful day for cookout. Kids rode bikes and had an awesome time and didn&amp;#8217;t want to leave. Got home and kids still rambunctious and played outside. Kaleena came over and ate with us. I got into a fight with Lesa and left for a couple of hours, had to decide whether I wanted to come back or not, came back for the kids&amp;#8217; sake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 9, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-9-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2019 22:48:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-9-2019/</guid>
      <description>Slept in! Got up before boys, quiet without Dillan and Ashley, or should I say quieter. Got the boys breakfast, they were playing with Dillan&amp;#8217;s stuff. Took boys with me to Tieman&amp;#8217;s in Owensburg to get tires for Lesa&amp;#8217;s Jeep, Bruce did nothing but complain. He survived and made it home alive. Ate lunch and then started getting trash together. Hauled trash, made the boys go with me, again they both survived relatively unscathed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 8, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-8-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 23:36:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-8-2019/</guid>
      <description>Friday, made sure Dillan and Ashley had their belongings for SuperStart. Gave them money for meals and souvenirs, drove all the kids to school and went in with them to add Ken to the sign out list. Got a couple dozen donuts for the shop and went to work. Ken picked the kids up early from school and they headed to New Albany/Louisville with the rest of the middle school youth group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 7, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-7-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 22:29:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-7-2019/</guid>
      <description>Got colder so Ashley and me stuffed more hay in the rabbit hutch to help keep them warm. Took kids to school. Slow day at work, $5 sushi day so got some per usual. Picked kids up. Ashley had Girl Scouts so I dropped her off at 6pm. Went back at 7pm for awards and talked to Alisha a lot about the school closings &amp;#8211; or should say she talked to me a lot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 6, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-6-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 00:10:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-6-2019/</guid>
      <description>Let Dillan know the teacher told us she already gave him his missing assignments. Let him know he&amp;#8217;d better get them home tonight, or he gets a whopping and SuperStart will go away. Took kids to school and went to work. Made Ashley an appointment with dermatologist for February, referral from the doctor after the last rash she had. Dillan had his missing papers when I picked the kids up from daycare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 5, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-5-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 22:56:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-5-2019/</guid>
      <description>Election Day, no school, dropped kids off at daycare. Received email overnight that mail had arrived at the PO Box so I went and got it after dropping them off. Had five letters all from Daniel with each one directed to the kids. The dates were Oct. 2, 10, 18, 25 and Nov. 1. I worked in Bloomington and tied to get access to NGA maps, submitted request and awaiting the Need-to-Know confirmation from Navy sponsor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 4, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-4-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 23:03:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-4-2019/</guid>
      <description>Kids wanted to sleep an extra hour again &amp;#8211; me too! Got them to school on time and headed to work. Went to Best Buys and got a CAC reader and then headed to SAIC. Finished the day out there and then picked up Dillan and Bruce from daycare. Home game against Parkview, Ashley was cheerleading, Dwyane was in Hornets Nest. Mrs Davis texted Ashley forgot her bow so went home and looked but didn&amp;#8217;t see it so went to game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 3, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-3-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 22:02:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-3-2019/</guid>
      <description>Family Sunday, Lockup Deacon. Ashley had a Girl Scout meeting of all things and it got canceled due to a death in Alisha Goodwine&amp;#8217;s family. The kids were constantly fighting so I made them go outside to play. Ashley wanted to process the persimmons we have so I showed her how, we were able to get 8 cups of pulp. Kids finely started playing well with each other. Ate supper and took Dillan and Ashley to youth group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 2, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-2-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 00:36:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-2-2019/</guid>
      <description>Didn&amp;#8217;t get to sleep in even though I really wanted too. Instead we all went to C3 and helped with Hope Harvest 2019. Signed all the kids up this year, they were a pain-in-the-butt but did pretty good for being kids. Three hours was about the limit though and thankfully we were done in that amount of time. Packed some 70,000 meals. I needed some sleep so Lesa took the boys to Lowe&amp;#8217;s and bought a couple of leaf rakes to give me a chance to take a nap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 1, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-1-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 23:44:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-1-2019/</guid>
      <description>Have to go to Atterbury again, hadn&amp;#8217;t planned on that, but didn&amp;#8217;t need to be there by 7a so I got to take the kids to school and drop them off. Nice morning but cold, leaves look awesome. Did some testing and SAIC guys starting breaking down equipment and basically we were chased out. By 3:30 I was off work! Picked up the kids and headed home. Lesa took PTO and went grocery shopping and installed the heated water bottle for the rabbits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 31, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-31-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 21:30:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-31-2019/</guid>
      <description>Halloween! It snowed! It was demo day at Atterbury, got there at 6:50am, was the first person to arrive, others started arriving around 7am. Lesa took kids to daycare and picked them up. Long day of work, very stressful but all went well. I got home about 6 and we got kids ready and took them to Cornerstone Church for their Fall Carnival. Kids got lots of candy and played a bunch of games and had their faces painted and knew lots of other kids so they had a really good time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 30, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-30-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 22:18:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-30-2019/</guid>
      <description>Up early to go to Camp Atterbury. Lesa got kids fed and to daycare. It rained all day and temps dropped. Had hard time in the curves and couldn&amp;#8217;t see squat. Everything is set up and ready for tomorrow so I got to leave just before lunch. So I called Lesa and asked if she wanted to go to Taste of India with me and absolutely, so I picked her up, and I pretty much talked shop the entire time, and then dropped her back off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 29, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-29-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 23:01:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-29-2019/</guid>
      <description>Another day at Camp Atterbury, two down, two to go. Left Atterbury early and headed to Scientia and tested a new build and actually got home before dark! Text from Mrs Davis: Dillan filled his test paper with emojis and turned it in. Then he typed random gobbledygook on a second paper; F&amp;#8217;s of course. I told him since he doesn&amp;#8217;t want to do school work I was going to make him do real work and he seemed okay with that, so I had him dig a hole in the woods for an hour &amp;#8211; he didn&amp;#8217;t make the hour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 28, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-28-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 21:00:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-28-2019/</guid>
      <description>Up at 5a, left at 5:30a for Atterbury. Left at 5:30p and home by 7p! Long day! Lesa dropped kids at daycare, daycare took them to school. Ashley stayed after for cheer practice, Lesa picked her up, then the boys. She took them all to Cub Scout Pack meeting. They got home at 7:15p. Ashley ran in crying Lesa said she&amp;#8217;d rather die than spend another minute in the car with them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 27, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-27-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2019 22:35:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-27-2019/</guid>
      <description>Church, paid for Dillan and Ashley to go to SuperStart. Lesa got mad at Dillan and me for horsing in the pews during the sermon. Ross and Bobbi Johnson&amp;#8217;s last day, most likely won&amp;#8217;t see them again. They gave kids some Matchbox toy cars. We took them and the Fries out to lunch at El Ranchero Mexican Restaurant in Bloomington, we all had a nice time &amp;#8211; even the kids. Always hard to lose good friends and decent people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 26, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-26-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2019 23:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-26-2019/</guid>
      <description>Rained pretty heavy all night and most of the day. Got up at 8a, took Dillan to guitar lesson and picked up Ashley. During lesson, Cassie, Emma, Woodrow, Ashley and myself went to Emma Miracle&amp;#8217;s to see the baby goats. Came home and Ashley very tired but won&amp;#8217;t nap. Ate lunch. Went to Rural King, got some stuff for the rabbits and chickens. Went to Walmart and got Ashley a pair of dress shoes and a pair of dress boots, got Dillan a new pair of mud boots, and Dwyane a pair of dress shoes as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 25, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-25-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 23:41:18 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-25-2019/</guid>
      <description>Took kids to school, Ashley going home with Cassie and Emma Tussey tonight after school, so checked her overnight bag and wrote a note so Cassie could get her. Dillan and the boys went to daycare. I wound up at Atterbury all day and didn&amp;#8217;t get home until after six. Lesa went grocery shopping, then picked up the boys. She dropped Dillan off at church for C3 Nerf Wars, Dillan was pissed because Ken used a paint gun and it hurt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 24, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-24-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 23:34:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-24-2019/</guid>
      <description>Dropped kids off at school. Went to Scientia, expected to go to Atterbury today but stayed to help a co-worker. Worker until 4:30p and then left to get kids from daycare. They had a little time to play before eating and after dinner played some more. The kids had some homework, Bruce sight words, Dwyane reading, Ashley reading, and Dillan spelling. Ashley got all her stuff ready for spending the night at Emma&amp;#8217;s tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 23, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-23-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 23:24:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-23-2019/</guid>
      <description>Took kids to school again. Worked at Scientia, then drove to Camp Atterbury and worked there until late afternoon so Lesa had to pick up the kids. She picked up Ashley from cheerleading practice and then picked up the boys from daycare. They had already eaten supper by the time I got home. The boys rode their bikes through mud puddles and had mud in their hair and elsewhere so they had to take showers for the second time in as many nights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 22, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-22-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 23:58:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-22-2019/</guid>
      <description>Took kids to school. Dropped truck off at Sturgis and had left front wheel bearing replaced. Worked at Scientia until 2p, luckily I wasn&amp;#8217;t need out at Camp Atterbury so I got to pick Ashley up from school. The boys rode the van to daycare per usual. I took Ashley to her first real cheerleading event for Springville Elementary at an away game. The girl and boy Basketball teams played Heltonville.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 21, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-21-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 23:21:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-21-2019/</guid>
      <description>Drove kids to school, drove to work. Drove the 4Runner, clutch pedal going to floor and not returning which kind of puts a damper on driving. Thought I&amp;#8217;d have to go to Camp Atterbury and possibly spend the night but no. Worked over a half hour and then picked up the kids from daycare. Rained all day so basically just stayed in and watched TV. Ashley&amp;#8217;s top to her uniform finally arrived and she was excited to show it off to us with a cheer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 20, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-20-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 00:06:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-20-2019/</guid>
      <description>Cincinnati Christian Church 100th Anniversary and they had a lunch and celebration, drew a huge crowd, all the deacons showed up at 9 and parked at library across the street. Ashley and Dillan came in early with me. Stayed for lunch and while kids played nine square outside we listened to some of the older folks stories about the church. It was kind of nice. Came home, kids played outside. Kaleena called, Ashley went to her house and the two of them showed up later at our house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 19, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-19-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2019 22:33:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-19-2019/</guid>
      <description>Got up early, Ashley and me went to the Tussey&amp;#8217;s along with Nicole Rogers. We slaughtered and butchered 30 chickens. Ashley and Emma helped. Emma got kicked by their donkey but is okay. Ashley did all stations except butchering and killing. Came home with a cooler full of meat birds. Dillan was riding dirt bike when we got home and the boys were riding bicycles. After showers Ashley joined the boys and I took a nap, Lesa went and got 20 pounds of ice to put on the birds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 18, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-18-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 23:32:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-18-2019/</guid>
      <description>Work, daycare, Lesa stayed home. Lesa went grocery shopping, Walmart, Rural King, got chicken stuff and kids some clothes. I went to Atterbury, kind of a busy day. Found out I&amp;#8217;ll probably be doing an all-nighter on this upcoming Tuesday. I&amp;#8217;ll be there most of next week and the following. Sucks for everyone especially Lesa who will need to handle the kids. She picked them up tonight. I got home late as expected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 17, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-17-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 23:14:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-17-2019/</guid>
      <description>Back to work for me, Lesa stayed home, kids went to daycare. Long, long day for everyone I think. Bruce aggravated Dillan at daycare, Dillan kicked Bruce and hurt him. Annetta called and said Bruce wasn&amp;#8217;t behaving his normal self, wouldn&amp;#8217;t eat, and just sat holding his side. He said it hurt really bad so she called me. She didn&amp;#8217;t think I needed to leave work early so I didn&amp;#8217;t. Lesa came up and we returned the rental.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 16, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-16-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 22:50:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-16-2019/</guid>
      <description>Got up early, got the kids breakfast, got packed and loaded, and left for home. Rained entire way in Tennessee and the wind was very strong in spots. Could tell it rained in Kentucky as well, but the wind lessened and made first stop just short of Lexington! Ate at Wendy&amp;#8217;s, service sucked. Plugged in Batman LEGO Movie. Ran 80-85 mph the entire time I was on an interstate and it really trimmed down our travel time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 15, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-15-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 22:03:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-15-2019/</guid>
      <description>Got up earlier, Ashley&amp;#8217;s ankle doing better. Went into Pigeon Forge to tour the Titanic Museum. I was worried the kids might get bored but they seemed to enjoy it. I was soured from the start when they made us wait an hour past our reserved time to let a travel club go in front of us. We were given identities that resembled our gender and age. All the kids and Lesa survived, I was killed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 14, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-14-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2019 21:20:40 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-14-2019/</guid>
      <description>Lazy morning probably cost us a chance at seeing black bears at Cades Cove and definitely left us in traffic on the Loop, however, the views were beautiful, we got to stop halfway around and have lunch at the most beautiful spot in the entire park. It was totally awesome. We stopped at man of the churches and cabins along the way. Ashley sprained her ankle on the steps horsing around with the boys so she slowed things up and limited some of what we could do, started hurting her really bad later in the day and each stop made it stiffen even more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 13, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-13-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2019 00:59:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-13-2019/</guid>
      <description>Lesa woke up to Dillan. I woke up to Lesa, the rest of the kids woke up to me. Ashley&amp;#8217;s rash is back &amp;#8211; on her back this time. Spent the day in the Smokey Mountain National Park. Started off at the Townsend entrance sign, then some little overlook with a small waterfall in the background. The Sinks were next, it&amp;#8217;s kind of a shame the kids couldn&amp;#8217;t explore on the rocks and stuff like Lesa and I did the last time we were here but it was also kind of a relief.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 12, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-12-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2019 00:37:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-12-2019/</guid>
      <description>Finished packing and loading the truck. Headed for the Smokies. Sonja is pet sitting. Took us 7 hours to get here. Had a decent trip. Kids are driving us crazy and I swore I was going to whip all of them &amp;#8211; multiple times &amp;#8211; but never did. Got to our place in Townsend, I thought it was a cabin but it was a house instead, really nice place and I have no complaints.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 11, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-11-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 22:22:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-11-2019/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8221;s Friday! Took kids to school and headed to work. Should have gotten off at 11:00am because of the time I put in at Atterbury on Wednesday but wound up working until 3:30pm giving me some more comp time. Met Lesa and we went to Budget to get our rental car, a Tahoe SUV. I picked up kids and Lesa fixed supper. Spent the evening getting prepped for tomorrow. Kids are very excited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 10, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-10-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 23:26:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-10-2019/</guid>
      <description>Kids glad I got them ready for school this morning, they love Lesa but yesterday was a departure from their normal routine. Dropped them off at school and headed to work. Thought I&amp;#8217;d be heading back to Atterbury but not, probably tomorrow. It&amp;#8217;s Thursday, which is $5 sushi day at Fresh Tyme, so I got some sushi for lunch. Left at 3:30p and made it just in time for Parent-Teacher Conferences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 9, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-9-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 22:00:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-9-2019/</guid>
      <description>Got up at 4am, out by 5am, off to Camp Atterbury to set up, install, and test. Lesa got kids up, fed, ready and off to daycare. Daycare van took them to school. Ashley didn&amp;#8217;t have cheerleading practice today, scheduled off last week. Lesa picked up the kids from daycare as well. I was at Camp Atterbury until 5:30pm and didn&amp;#8217;t get home until 7:00pm. Everyone glad to see me and I&amp;#8217;m glad to be home, Lesa stopped by CVS before picking up kids to get medicine for pin worms and gave each kid their dose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 8, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-8-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 21:44:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-8-2019/</guid>
      <description>Dropped kids off at school, left off on time, and picked up kids. Lesa went grocery shopping after work so we beat her home. Kids played outside together and actually got along with each other. They are getting excited about going to the Smokies. Lesa took Girl Scout sales money to Amanda after we got the amount due calculated, I watched the kids and got them all in the shower. Ashley said she had a question, and told me that when she wiped she saw something crawling and she wanted me to look, so I did, and sure enough she had little white worms in her anus, took a sample with tweezers and looked them up, they are called thread or pin worms and can be treated with over-the-counter medicine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 7, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-7-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 22:50:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-7-2019/</guid>
      <description>Lesa made Ashley&amp;#8217;s lunch since she was in no shape to do so herself, I wrote a note and put it in her lunch. Dropped the kids off at school. Ashley went on a field trip to West Gate and Odon Park, they had a good time, Ashley brought home a solar oven she made. Took the boys to Cub Scouts, a Bedford police officer spoke with Wolves, Dwyane group. He turned on lights but not the siren.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 6, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-6-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 22:31:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-6-2019/</guid>
      <description>Stayed home from church, everyone utterly exhausted, especially Lesa. Leisurely morning. I picked up Ashley at 12:30p and she was ready to come home. They got wet, no fly on the tent, and when it began raining they just threw the fly on top but the girls had a good time. I took Dillan to his guitar lesson at 2p, Ken revealed to Dillan the top 4, or was it 5, secrets of being a guitar player.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 5, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-5-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 04:06:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-5-2019/</guid>
      <description>Lesa and I woke up to my 8:00am alarm. Lesa got up, I tried to snooze more but unable. Kids were still asleep! Dogs rushed into Ashley&amp;#8217;s room and nuzzled her and she woke up, the boys followed. Even our dogs love the kids! Got the Cub Scout boys ready for selling popcorn, had to get mad and light a fire under them to get them moving. Bruce was his usual grumpy self, complained about everything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 4, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-4-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 01:07:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-4-2019/</guid>
      <description>Got Ashley to pack all her cheerleading stuff, took care of animals, and drove kids to school. Thought I was going to get off at noon since I worked last Sunday so I had asked Lesa to go on a date lunch but she couldn&amp;#8217;t go so a good thing since I would up having to work anyway, turned my overtime into comp time for upcoming holidays. Got put in charge of the map program at work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 3, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-3-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 23:01:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-3-2019/</guid>
      <description>My birthday, 58, an old man and feel it too, text from my dad, kids woke up trying to give me notes and presents, had to ask them to wait until evening during my party. Drove them to school again, called Mr Hudson and talked to him myself, got a good understanding of what happened, just kids being kids and parents (Kensie&amp;#8217;s) over-reacting. Lesa sent me chocolates at work for my birthday!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 2, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-2-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 22:36:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-2-2019/</guid>
      <description>Drove kids to school. Dwyane took a field trip to Spring Mill and had a picnic there, took a hike, visited the Grissom Space Center and played on the playground, according to Dwyane he had a great day. Mr Hudson talked to Kensie and Ashley again! Left a message on the machine but I didn&amp;#8217;t get to hear it because Lesa accidentally erased it. Lesa picked up Ashley from cheer practice, then picked up the boys from daycare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 1, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-1-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 23:39:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-1-2019/</guid>
      <description>Let boys ride bus, took Ashley to school. Left a message for Mr Hudson to call and fill me in on what actually happened but didn&amp;#8217;t return my call. Dillan had rash on his face now, all around his eyes, and he&amp;#8217;s been rubbing it, took a look and decided to call doctor for him too, Lesa was able to rearrange her work schedule to take him and then worked from home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 30, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-30-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 23:49:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-30-2019/</guid>
      <description>Barely made bus, kids ran to get on, Axsoms started yelling at Ashley. Tried asking what was up but they drove off, I followed, wound up in the parking lot of the liquor store in Oolitic. Axsoms said Ashley shoved Kensie getting on bus, and Kensie said Ashley made her eat paper and has been bullying her. I didn&amp;#8217;t see the shoving thing but the bullying did happen last week, and so I told them I&amp;#8217;d take care of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 29, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-29-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2019 23:01:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-29-2019/</guid>
      <description>Took kids to Sunday School and church, Lesa stayed home, Ashley sold lots of Girl Scout candy. After lunch I had to work, everyone decided to go with, kids played in gym on treadmill, elliptical, and with weight machines. Late when we finally left and decided to eat at Asian Pearl. Kids played and watched TV until bedtime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 28, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-28-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2019 00:15:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-28-2019/</guid>
      <description>Ashley&amp;#8217;s rash all over her neck, called and made another appointment, suspect it may be biological &amp;#8211; like strep or something. Lesa too Dillan to guitar lesson while I toted remaining kids around. Got them a Frosty after the doctor&amp;#8217;s visit, then CVS for different meds and a topical cream. Lesa called no to persimmon festival. I spent the afternoon preparing the Greek salad and the souvlaki &amp;#8211; dinner was awesome,!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 27, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-27-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 23:52:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-27-2019/</guid>
      <description>Finally Friday, seemed like a very long week. Kids rode bus. Lesa went grocery shopping, got bulk of my Greek dinner items, I got remaining from Fresh Thyme before picking up the kids up from daycare. Lesa picked up pizza from Papa John&amp;#8217;s. Let the kids watch a movie &amp;#8211; even Dillan and Ashley. &amp;#8211; I ended their grounding early. Made Tzatziki and put in fridge, and made marinade and added chicken breasts and refrigerated as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 26, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-26-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2019 00:40:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-26-2019/</guid>
      <description>Ashley&amp;#8217;s last day taking Prednisone, how her behavior improves and she feels better. Dropped the kids off at school, spent way too much time getting ready and taking care of animals. Work stressful, sucks, not sure where I stand, not sure why they keep me around. Jerry Davis texted and me and kids met him and Michelle at Springville Store so I could pay him for bush hogging new property, chatted awhile, kids said they missed Michelle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 25, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-25-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 23:08:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-25-2019/</guid>
      <description>Took kids to bus stop, had to go back home so Ashley could take her pill and to write Dillan an excuse to get into class. Lesa liked her flowers. Long work day, crashed a video encoder at end of the day, almost late picking up boys. Ashley had cheerleader practice, Lesa picked her up. Met the girls up on our new property along with Mike Pearson. We discussed land layout among other things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 24, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-24-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 22:34:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-24-2019/</guid>
      <description>Bruce woke me up to let me know Dillan had vomited from the top of the triple bunk bed and it went everywhere. Clean up on aisle 1. Got the rest of the kids up, fed, and ready for school. Lesa worked from home and Dillan went back to sleep. A couple hours later he was good to go. Her flowers got delivered but she wasn&amp;#8217;t there. Ashley brought his homework home for him and all the kids had homework of one kind or another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 23, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-23-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 22:28:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-23-2019/</guid>
      <description>Ashley&amp;#8217;s face better already after just one round of Prednisone. Worked at SAIC all day. Ordered flowers via FTD for Lesa &amp;#8211; just because. Grounded Dillan and Ashley from TV for two and one week respectively for fighting with each other. Ashley antagonized Dillan by taking his seat at daycare and Dillan retaliated by hitting and kicking and hurting her. Dillan got two because he was just in the principal&amp;#8217;s office last Friday for pretty much the same thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 22, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-22-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 00:41:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-22-2019/</guid>
      <description>Ashley&amp;#8217;s face much worse. Church, Junior Church with Ashley, Dwyane and Bruce. Dillan was in sanctuary with Lesa. Ashley sold lots of candy. Got Ashley a doctor appointment right after church so got her there right away, Prednisone alike last time, but this time tablets, and 20mg at that, made her get super hyper and hungry. Picked up a new GS order form from Amanda. Ate lunch at Taco Bell. At home tried to nap, guess I fell asleep for awhile, woke up and heard neighbor riding ATV around our loop again, Dillan and Bruce rode bikes through his yard and messed up his stone border.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 21, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-21-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 00:30:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-21-2019/</guid>
      <description>Scheduling hell, Lesa had girls day out with Andrea and Bobbie. I was supposed to go fishing and rent boat with Paul and Ross and kids. Ashley had a GS Horseback Riding event. Lesa canceled fishing for me after scheduling fishing for me. Anyway, Ashley woke up with allergic reaction on her face, called doctor, suggested Benadryl, didn&amp;#8217;t help like we knew it wouldn&amp;#8217;t. Got a plate for the 4Runner, chicken and rabbit feed, and took the kids to lunch at Steak &amp;#8216;n&amp;#8217; Shake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 20, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-20-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 23:44:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-20-2019/</guid>
      <description>Friday, kids rode bus. Drove Suburban, miss is gone, fixed for $56, happy. Worked in Bloomington until 11:00, then drove disk to SAIC, tested and left for the day. Picked up Lesa, and we went to school for Grandparent&amp;#8217;s Day. As we walked in Mr Hudson intercepted us and pointed Dillan out sitting in the office, he hit Ashley in the back, and when he was told to stop, he got mad, threw a ball that hit a bucket that hit a girl in the mouth and busted her lip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 19, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-19-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 00:11:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-19-2019/</guid>
      <description>Drove 4Runner again. Boys rode bus, I forgot my teeth, Ashley wanted to stay with me when I went back for them, so I dropped her off at school. Delivered disk to SAIC then worked in Bloomington for the remainder of the day &amp;#8211; felt wiped out all day long. Lesa drove Ashley to her Girl Scout meeting at Fayetteville Elementary. I tried to get a nap in after dinner but that didn&amp;#8217;t happen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 18, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-18-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 01:30:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-18-2019/</guid>
      <description>Kids thought it was cool to ride in the 4Runner, they all like it. Bus, work, busy day, had 6 hours overtime last week, would have more this week except I&amp;#8217;m taking a half day on Friday. Work is a bear, got home and started working, worked past midnight, Ashley says I get bitchy when I have to work at home and she doesn&amp;#8217;t like it. Second night of math with Dillan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 17, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-17-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 23:22:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-17-2019/</guid>
      <description>Kids caught bus per usual. Drove the Suburban, it was missing out from the moment I started it, actually worried about getting to work and back and worried about being stuck on side of the road with four kids too. Ashley remembered her GS Candy order form and made some sales at school. Dillan had a really bad grade on his math pretest so I made him rework the entire pretest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 16, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-16-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2019 22:15:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-16-2019/</guid>
      <description>Ashley had bad start to day, couldn&amp;#8217;t find her GS order form. Truck had a bad miss when I started it this morning. Got to work okay. Long, rough day. Truck stilling running bad on way to get kids and home. Took Dwyane and Bruce to Cub Scouts, Ashley did her reading homework, Dillan did multiplication flashcards. Started a daily Bible study with Ashley and Lesa and I kind of hope she sticks with it and maybe Dillan join too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 15, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-15-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 23:03:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-15-2019/</guid>
      <description>Church, lead deacon in back, security also. After church went to work and picked up Toyota 4-Runner I bought off Todd Davidson. Lesa followed me in Suburban and kids rode with me, they were excited to ride in something new and were amazed at the stick shift. Ashley went to Kaleena&amp;#8217;s and Dillan to Gabe&amp;#8217;s. Gary Flynn&amp;#8217;s son and grandson were riding their motorcycles around our loop, Dillan called them butt holes, whole thing exploded into an argument but sort of smoothed over but not really resolved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 14, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-14-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 23:32:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-14-2019/</guid>
      <description>Woke up about 4:00am in tent, took boys to bathroom, went back to sleep until 6:20am. Got up, another parent started stoking fire, I broke out camp stove and started coffee. Wound up making four pots for folks, and scrambling six dozen eggs. Dwyane ate nearly an entire bag of donuts, Bruce ate what he didn&amp;#8217;t. Broke camp after breakfast and took boys to Shoot-O-Ree. Their favorite things were fishing rod casting, Marshmallow shooters, and catapults.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 13, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-13-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 23:05:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-13-2019/</guid>
      <description>Friday the 13th plus a full moon. Worked a full day even though I tried to get out of there to go camping. Lesa tried to help by going into, and leaving, work early. Got pizza from Papa John&amp;#8217;s. Smattering of rain in the afternoon but quickly stopped. Jordan sent a link to the finished PAVA photos. Got the kids, packed up the truck, said goodbyes and the boys and me went to camp and the Shoot-O-Ree tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 12, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-12-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 22:53:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-12-2019/</guid>
      <description>We all got up at 5:00a, I had a fasting lab at 7:15a so I needed to drop kids off at daycare and let daycare take them to school. Boys have been helping with chicks, Ashley so-so taking care of rabbits. Lesa rushed to have supper, I rushed to get kids, Ashley had her Girl Scout meeting and they&amp;#8217;re selling nuts and candies. Lesa bought some, and then she pestered me and when I didn&amp;#8217;t respond as quickly as she thought I should she started crying and accusing me of not loving her, half hour later she was better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 11, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-11-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 22:41:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-11-2019/</guid>
      <description>School, work. Mr Hudson called, Bruce got into a fight with a kid on the playground, started out friendly roughhousing that turned into to rough, had to go to his office and again during recess for remainder of the week. Ashley had cheerleader practice, Lesa picked her up, she did a couple of cheers for us. Dillan brought home a 32% on his school work and I got made and lectured him about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 10, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-10-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 11:14:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-10-2019/</guid>
      <description>Normal morning. Worked late again. Picture retake forms came home with Ashley. Picked up kids at last minute. Got gas and went to Dollar General and restocked the candy supply. Lesa had supper ready by the time we got home. Kids rode bikes after dinner but that didn&amp;#8217;t last long. Helped Ashley clean out rabbit hutch, then I cleaned the fryers&amp;#8217; coop. All the kids were super hot and sweaty so showers were next.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 9, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-9-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 23:28:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-9-2019/</guid>
      <description>Normal morning, kids rode bus. Worked half a day in Bloomington and half the day in Bedford. Lesa took Ashley out of school early and took her to the dentist, spacer is okay but tooth is getting loose and will fall out soon. Kept really busy and worked until 4:30. Picked up kids around 5:00pm. After dinner I took boys to their Cub Scout meeting, they did announcements and meeting inside before heading outside to play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 8, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-8-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 23:31:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-8-2019/</guid>
      <description>Serving deacon, Dillan and Ashley got Baptism Certificates and Bible Study books from Tonya Johnson and church, visited Nancy Huffman and Gladys Gilland. Ate lunch at Burger King. Dwyane needed new tires and tubes plus an entire wheel since the bearings are blown out so Lesa and I decided we&amp;#8217;d make it a Dad and Dwyane outing to Walmart. Inner tubes and wheel alone cost nearly as much as a new bike, plus they didn&amp;#8217;t have a wheel, so Dwyane got to pick out a new bike!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 7, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-7-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2019 23:43:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-7-2019/</guid>
      <description>Got up early and dressed for our 2019 PAVA photo shoot at Southeastway Park in Indy. Jordan took photos again per tradition. Shot in a different location than the rock this year, took the photos near the pond. The kids did pretty well and then started getting bored of course. Afterward, we had a picnic lunch and let the kids play on the playground. We noticed 456 South westbound lanes were closed so we had to drive through Wanamaker and Greenwood to get back to Highway 37 and home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 6, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-6-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2019 23:10:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-6-2019/</guid>
      <description>Friday! Really rough day for me, stressed at work, entire side buzzed so bad it hurt, it still does. Lesa has most of the Fall Break trip planned, has an Airbnb, and a car rented &amp;#8211; a cabin in the Smokey&amp;#8217;s and a minivan. Midterms: Dillan As, Bs, Cs and 3 Ds, and an evaluation stating he&amp;#8217;s at performing at a 2nd grade level; Ashley As and 2 Bs; ditto for Dwyane and a pleasure to have note; and Bruce no grades but a positive note.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 5, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-5-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 22:31:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-5-2019/</guid>
      <description>Normal AM. Worked a long day again. Kids got their school photos. Bruce looks so stinking cute except for his face is all mangled from scrapes and cuts. Dwyane&amp;#8217;s tooth is crooked and in front of the others giving his this weird kind of smile. Ashley looks exactly like Nicolle, Lesa doesn&amp;#8217;t think so much. Dillan looks good and with a decent smile for once. At dinner all the kids tattled on everyone else&amp;#8217;s girlfriend/boyfriends &amp;#8211; none of them really have one &amp;#8211; just teasing each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 4, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-4-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 22:03:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-4-2019/</guid>
      <description>Same morning routine: Dwyane and Bruce big chickens, Ashley rabbits, and me the chicks. Bus on time. Started workday at SAIC and ended at Scientia. Another rough day, afternoon got better. Haven&amp;#8217;t had a headache in quite a while but have one now. Lesa texted to let me know highway already backed up, she barely made it in time to get Ashley from cheerleader practice, they learned the Wipeout &amp;#8211; whatever that is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 3, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-3-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 22:56:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-3-2019/</guid>
      <description>Got kids up, everyone tired per usual, bowl of Fruit Loops for everyone to finish them off. Bruce and Dwyane took care of the big chickens, Ashley her rabbits, and me the fryer chicks, made bus easily. Dillan and Ashley got I-STEP results from last year, Dillan below average, Ashley above. Work was a bear. Left an hour late, construction on highway backed up for miles, had to call Lesa to get kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 2, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-2-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 23:23:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-2-2019/</guid>
      <description>Labor Day, no school, no work. Everyone slept in a little bit. The kids were cracking up when I started reading some of the old kid quotes. Kids very rambunctious and Lesa decided they needed exercise so after lunch we took them to Milwaukee Trail and walked to Wilson Park and back, that solved that. Took them to Jiffy Treat and stopped for milk before heading home. Dillan helped me put away tent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 1, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-1-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 22:07:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-1-2019/</guid>
      <description>Woke up to Nerf gun fight in the house. Put a stop to that and started breakfast. Skipped church, everyone up too late, needed the sleep. Dillan and Gabe went to his house around 9, came back half-an-hour later with Gracie. All the kids had fun playing with each other even tough Lesa and I had our fill. They ate lunch with us and we sent them home. We discussed the night with Dillan and Ashley because we really didn&amp;#8217;t like some of the behavior we saw.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 31, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--august-31-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 01:34:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--august-31-2019/</guid>
      <description>Took Dillan to guitar lessons, not sure if he&amp;#8217;s learning anything but he seems to enjoy going, doesn&amp;#8217;t practice much. After lunch we all went with Lesa to get her hair cut at Fantastic Sams in Bedford and then went to Walmart to get Ashley some white tennis shoes for cheerleading. Let the kids get donuts too. Set up the tent for Dillan and Gabe, he&amp;#8217;s spending the night. Built a fire, we all joined in on marshmallows and s&amp;#8217;mores and hot dogs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 30, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-30-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 22:42:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-30-2019/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217;s Friday and Labor Day weekend, we get Monday off. Totally missed the bus, dropped kids off at school. Payday Friday, so I bought donuts for the shop per usual. Long, long day! Got off work at 3:00p and even gave them an extra hour. Took long leisurely drive through the countryside to pick up kids, truck started having transmission problems half way there, didn&amp;#8217;t want to pull or kick down into lower gear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 29, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-29-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 22:02:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-29-2019/</guid>
      <description>Barely made the bus, Kim waited for the kids to get on board. Took an alternate, scenic route to work, highway under construction and down to one lane. Spent most of day doing research. Lesa having her own problems at work. Both of us pretty zoned out by the time we get home. Mrs. Davis texted us, Dillan punched William in the eye and got in trouble for it. I was none to happy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 28, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-28-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 23:54:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-28-2019/</guid>
      <description>Better at getting ready this morning, managed to get everything done, made bus easily. Scientia all day, got a crap load done even with build issues. Boys seemed ready to go home when I picked them up. Ashley had cheer practice, issues over her shoes not being good enough, learned movements to last weeks&amp;#8217; cheer, Lesa picked her up at school after practice. Dillan has brought his agenda home last two nights, did okay work for Dillan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 27, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-27-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 23:21:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-27-2019/</guid>
      <description>Kids still tired after getting up, missed bus, dropped them off at school. Started workday at SAIC and went to Scientia mid-morning. Picked up kids late, they were making slime and got upset with me for coming so early. Ashley didn&amp;#8217;t take care of her rabbits until we got on her. She was having troubles, talked back to us a lot, got emotional a few times. Dillan had multiple meltdowns over doing his homework, cried, and general didn&amp;#8217;t want to do it, total drama.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 26, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-26-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 22:45:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-26-2019/</guid>
      <description>Monday. Rained all night, downpour sprung live trap, fixed chicks tarp in preparation of storms, and still made bus on time. Worked in Bloomington and then SAIC around noon for rest of the day. Got ECT sensor from NAPA, then picked up kids. Kids stuck inside, boys not too bad, Ashley a mess, meltdown on lack of friends, another because Lesa doesn&amp;#8217;t love her enough, thinks she gets into trouble for disrespecting when Dillan pees the bed, blah, blah, blah, drama!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 25, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-25-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 23:32:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-25-2019/</guid>
      <description>Slept in, skipped church, everyone needed the extra rest. Got a young opossum in the live trap; Dillan, Bruce and I released it near Springville Cemetery West. After lunch, we went to Mike Pearson&amp;#8217;s to discuss the house, going forward, Lesa is comfortable, more so than me. Kids took A/V ride down to Ken and Cassie&amp;#8217;s place, we picked them up there, they were getting A/V rides and checked out a cave on their property.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 24, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-24-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 00:28:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-24-2019/</guid>
      <description>Woke up to kids screaming and putting their hands on each other &amp;#8211; idiot, stupid, butt head, etc. Grounded all of them from screens of all types for entire weekend: no TV, tablets, phones, YouTube on computer, clock on microwave, etc. It was like we sentenced them to hell judging by all the wails, moans and groans we received. Went to Rural King and bought Ashley&amp;#8217;s pet play area, would be great for chickens, will be used for rabbits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 23, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-23-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 23:12:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-23-2019/</guid>
      <description>Friday, long week! Missed bus taking care of chickens and rabbits but not late, still beat bus riders. Got off and picked up kids early, boys played in mud, Ashley read for 40 minutes per assignment. Lesa grocery shopped. Pizza. Watched Open Season I and II. Kids had a good time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 22, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-22-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 22:34:18 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-22-2019/</guid>
      <description>School and work. Busy day. Rained. Lesa picked up kids, took them to school, Girl Scouts had signup event and Ashley was a part of it. I picked her up. Got home and everyone had ate supper but us! We were only gone 10 minutes. American Ninja Warrior for rest of night. Kids tired!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 21, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-21-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 23:37:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-21-2019/</guid>
      <description>Chick fine. Texts from Albert, Boy Scout leader, pissing me off. Bus, school, daycare. Long productive work day. Lesa 5 miles on Fitbit by 10a! Ashley&amp;#8217;s first day of cheerleading practice, went well, Lesa picked up Ashley. I got boys, then got girls, we ate at Buffalo Wild Wings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 20, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-20-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 23:37:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-20-2019/</guid>
      <description>School, work. A chick not well. Stormed. Left early, Lesa and I met with Hoosier Hills about construction loan. Took Dillan to Scouts, says he was bullied, pushed, threatened; not sure what happened, feel like Dillan exaggerated boys being boys; regardless, he doesn&amp;#8217;t want to go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 19, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-19-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 00:09:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-19-2019/</guid>
      <description>School, work, kids missed bus messing around. Truck running bad. Boys had Cub Scouts, got their books, Ashley went with. Ashley hit Bruce in drive-by, I did same to her, she went into drama mode, maybe she&amp;#8217;ll stop? Dillan brought school papers home, had 40% on last spelling test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 18, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-18-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2019 23:02:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-18-2019/</guid>
      <description>Church, kid&amp;#8217;s first communion, Dillan spilled on his pants. Lesa took Ashley shopping for white sport bra for cheerleading. After chores Dillan went to Gabe&amp;#8217;s, boys tablet time. Ashley unloaded/loaded dishwasher, got tablet too. Kids total asses to each other. Wouldn&amp;#8217;t go to bed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 17, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-17-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2019 23:47:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-17-2019/</guid>
      <description>Took Dillan to his first guitar lesson by Ken Tussey, Dillan didn&amp;rsquo;t offer much feedback. Picked up 6 fryers, fixed up brooder coop, Rural King for supplies. Got a little rain. Dillan played at Gabe&amp;rsquo;s. Everybody fighting, Lesa and Ashley going at it, I&amp;rsquo;m the bad guy always. Baths.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 16, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-16-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 21:43:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-16-2019/</guid>
      <description>Bed trashed my back, too soft. School picture day, kids looked good when they left, except Bruce with his scraped up face. Work okay, glad it&amp;#8217;s Friday. Lesa grocery shopped. I picked up kids, got home in time to help carry groceries. Pizza and a movie, watched Avengers, End Game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 15, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-15-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 22:32:18 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-15-2019/</guid>
      <description>New bed okay, we both thought it was hot but slept well. School bus by mere seconds! Worked late, barely got kids in time, no time for Ashley to eat dinner before Lesa drove her to Scouts. Boys played. I picked her up. Told her to take care of rabbits or else, cried, super tired!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 14, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-14-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 23:19:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-14-2019/</guid>
      <description>Kids had school; Lesa took PTO to clean bedroom; I worked from home. Took delivery of bedroom suite, our first, only took 37 years! Lunch with Lesa at McAlister&amp;#8217;s. Helped Lesa rearrange and clean bedroom. Picked up kids. Nothing scheduled, kids spent evening playing, watching TV.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 13, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-13-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 23:06:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-13-2019/</guid>
      <description>School, work, SAIC again. Got kids early. Started to fix shower drain, needed &amp;#8216;O&amp;#8217; ring, Lowe&amp;#8217;s with kids. Frosties. Finished drain, Dillan went into crawlspace with me, held light. Lesa took Dillan to Boy Scouts. Changed ECT sensor. Got Dillan, mad at me, said no to camp in Ohio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 12, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-12-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 22:22:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-12-2019/</guid>
      <description>School, IU, Scientia and SAIC. Truck overheating, put in thermostat, fans not kicking on, will try sensor tomorrow. Located shower drain after trying four places. Took Dwyane and Bruce to Cub Scouts, Ashley went with, Bruce misbehaved. Dillan helped me put deck belt on lawnmower.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 11, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-11-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2019 22:59:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-11-2019/</guid>
      <description>Church. I baptized Ashley and Dillan! Praise God! How awesome is that‽ We took Kathy Mitchell and Paul and Andrea Fries to El Ranchero for lunch, we all had a great time! Fantastic Sams for kid haircuts. Bought Lesa bedroom suite/mattress at Living Room Center. Truck overheating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 10, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-10-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 23:37:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-10-2019/</guid>
      <description>Kind of slept in, hauled trash, Lowe&amp;#8217;s for rabbit playpen materials. Tried fixing leaky shower drain, couldn&amp;#8217;t find supplies. Started building playpen with Ashley. Cub Scout End of Summer Pool Party, Ashley invited Emma, thought she would spend night but didn&amp;#8217;t. Everyone had fun!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 9, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-9-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 23:25:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-9-2019/</guid>
      <description>Friday! Everyone tired, even kids. Worked, kids school/daycare. Bruce tried handstand at daycare, wound up face planting, rug burns/scrapes week before school pics. Abraham&amp;#8217;s last day, my job just got harder. Pizza and movie, Ashley won but let Bruce pick The Secret Life of Pets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 8, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-8-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 22:07:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-8-2019/</guid>
      <description>School, daycare for kids. Work for Lesa and me. Kids obviously tired but handled it well. Fought like cats and dogs at breakfast, made them get down. Mrs Malone texted us to say Ashley is a doll and she enjoys having her in class. Ashley gave us massages. American Ninja Warriors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 7, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-7-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 22:57:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-7-2019/</guid>
      <description>School day #2, rode bus, no homework, kids still excited, phone blew up from pics/notes. Took Lesa to lunch at Taste of India, had their buffet, very nice break from hectic work day. Two minutes past cutoff getting kids, no one noticed. Kids chatter boxes talking about their day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 6, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-6-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 22:38:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-6-2019/</guid>
      <description>First day of 2019-2020 school year! Rode bus. Bruce 1st, Dwyane 2nd, Ashley 4th, Dillan 5th. Wow! Mrs Willis, Mrs Day, Mrs Malone, Mrs Davis. No homework, teachers/pupils getting to know each other. Little Starr&amp;#8217;s. They had good day, could tell they were tired. Rest of us worked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 5, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-5-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 22:13:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-5-2019/</guid>
      <description>Daycare, work, Lesa worked from home. She took Ashley and Dwyane to doctor for their physicals, took them to daycare after. Picked kids up, picked Lesa up, headed to school for Teacher Meet and Greet, got info and put up their supplies. Showers all around. Bed earlier than usual.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 4, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-4-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 23:36:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-4-2019/</guid>
      <description>Family Sunday, kids sang. Went to Bloomington, ate at Cozy Table on 3rd. Went to Kohl&amp;#8217;s for school shoes. On Great Clips sign-up list &amp;#8211; bumped us anyway &amp;#8211; never going back! Lowe&amp;#8217;s. Went to barber in Bedford, booked for rest of day. Walmart. Fixed Bruce&amp;#8217;s bike. Grilled salmon. TV.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 3, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-3-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 22:28:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-3-2019/</guid>
      <description>Slept in, kids sitting quietly in living room, first time ever. Ashley bridged from Brownie to Junior, it was nice. Boys rode bikes and played while Lesa and Ashley ordered school cloths. Water main broke. Nicole&amp;#8217;s, slaughtered Ken Tussey&amp;#8217;s meat chickens. Tacos, TV, showers, bed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 2, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-2-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 01:26:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-2-2019/</guid>
      <description>Friday! Work week finally over. Daycare, IU, Scientia. Did nothing after picking up kids, nice not having to rush someplace. Pizza and a movie &amp;#8211; not! Kids fighting over seats, and movie, so ate at table with us. Settled enough afterward to watch new Disney movie Dumbo on Blu-Ray.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 1, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-1-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 23:56:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-1-2019/</guid>
      <description>Caught raccoon in live-trap again. Daycare, Jessica&amp;#8217;s pool. Dr Hoff called, no blood in urine, PSA went from 4.6 to 1.6, follow-up January, every 6 months thereafter. It&amp;#8217;s great news, on Tuesday I had 5 year expectancy. Lesa took boys to last night of swim lessons, passed, party!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>