<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News-and-links.baks on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</title>
    <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/news-and-links.bak/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News-and-links.baks on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2013-{year} David E. Williams. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2007 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/news-and-links.bak/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dustin Levi Kelley (1988-2007) - Find A Grave Memorial</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/news-and-links.bak/2007/2007-10-13-dustin-levi-kelley-findagrave/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2007 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/news-and-links.bak/2007/2007-10-13-dustin-levi-kelley-findagrave/</guid>
      <description>Dustin Levi Kelley (1988-2007) View Dustin Levi Kelley (1988-2007) PDF Birth: 20 Dec 1988
Death: 8 Oct 2007 (aged 18)
Burial: Fairmount Cemetery, Huntingburg, Dubois County, Indiana, USA
Plot: Cremation
Memorial ID: 22154856
Dustin (18) died at about 10:30 am Monday in an automobile accident near the Huntingburg Conservation Club. He was born in MI to Karen Kelley of Huntingburg &amp;amp; Anthony McNeely of Washington. Surviving are his father, Anthony McNeely, and step-mother Anita McNeely of Washington; two brothers, Nathan &amp;amp; Zachary McNeely of Washington; one sister, Tosha McNeely of Huntingburg; three step-brothers, Daniel Eversole, Zachary Eversole and Dalton Moore of Washington; grandfather Carl Thomas McNeely of Washington; grandmother Francis McNeely of Bicknell; four uncles, Andrew McNeely and Jeff Lowe both of Evansville, Mark Petry of Dale, and Michael Petry of Huntingburg, two aunts, Clarissa Collins of Odon and Carla White of Bicknell; mother Karen Kelley of Huntingburg; grandparents Buck &amp;amp; Mary Kelley of Huntingburg, two uncles John Kelley of Florida and Keith Kelley of Texas; two aunts, Kim &amp;amp; Kay Kelley of Holland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Washington Times Herald Obituaries – Dustin’s Story</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/news-and-links.bak/2007/2007-10-08-dustins-story-washington-times-herald/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2007 00:00:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/news-and-links.bak/2007/2007-10-08-dustins-story-washington-times-herald/</guid>
      <description>Dustin Kelley View Dustin Kelley PDF Dustin&amp;#8217;s Story HUNTINGBURG &amp;#8211; Dustin Levi Kelley, 18, died at about 10:30 a.m. Monday in an automobile accident near the Huntingburg Conservation Club.
He was born in Michigan to Karen Kelley of Huntingburg and Anthony McNeely of Washington.
Surviving are his father, Anthony McNeely and stepmother Anita McNeely of Washington; two brothers, Nathan and Zachary McNeely, both of Washington; one sister, Tosha McNeely of Huntingburg; three stepbrothers, Daniel Eversole, Zachary Eversole and Dalton Moore of Washington; grandfather, Carl Thomas McNeely of Washington; grandmother, Frances McNeely of Bicknell; two aunts, Clarissa Collins of Odon and Carla White of Bicknell; three uncles, Andrew McNeely and Jeff Lowe, both of Evansville, Mark Petry of Dale, and Michael Petry of Huntingburg; mother, Karen Kelley of Huntingburg; grandparents, Buck and Mary Kelley of Huntingburg; two uncles, John Kelley of Florida and Keith Kelley of Texas; two aunts, Kim and Kay Kelley of Holland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Washington Times Herald – Veale Tosses Perfect Game for Hatchets</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/news-and-links.bak/2007/2007-05-11-washington-times-herald-veale-tosses-perfect-game-for-hatchets/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2007 11:39:44 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/news-and-links.bak/2007/2007-05-11-washington-times-herald-veale-tosses-perfect-game-for-hatchets/</guid>
      <description>Veale tosses perfect game for Hatchets View Veale tosses perfect game for Hatchets PDF If Kendra Veale ever wondered just how well she could pitch, then a quick viewing of the Barr-Reeve-Washington gametape might give her a pretty good indication.
Veale tossed a perfect game, mowing down all 21 Lady Vikings she faced on Thursday at the Sports Complex.
&amp;#8220;She pitched a heck of a game and we gave her the game ball after the game,&amp;#8221; said WHS coach Alan Lemon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Washington Times Herald – Hatchets Blast Past Shoals</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/news-and-links.bak/2007/2007-05-01-washington-times-herald-hatchets-blast-past-shoals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2007 11:34:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/news-and-links.bak/2007/2007-05-01-washington-times-herald-hatchets-blast-past-shoals/</guid>
      <description>Hatchets blast past Shoals View Hatchets blast past Shoals PDF What&amp;#8217;s better than back-to-back triples? Back-to-back triples, followed by an inside-the-park home run.
And that is exactly what the Hatchet softball team experienced, during a a 12-0 drubbing of Shoals on Monday at the Sports Complex.
And as coach Alan Lemon likes to say, &amp;#8220;They hit the ball with hardness.&amp;#8221;
The triples from Kendra Veale and Michelle Hulsey, was followed by the dinger from Kiersten Hinkle in a first inning that saw the Hatchets score 11 runs on 10 hits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Washington Times Herald – Hatchets Down Lady Lions</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/news-and-links.bak/2007/2007-04-13-washington-times-herald-hatchets-down-lady-lions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2007 22:23:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/news-and-links.bak/2007/2007-04-13-washington-times-herald-hatchets-down-lady-lions/</guid>
      <description>Hatchets Down Lady Lions View Hatchets Down Lady Lions PDF The Washington Hatchet softball team started the week playing well against North Daviess and finished it playing even better, with the season&amp;#8217;s first win, a 6-0 win over Loogootee.
The Hatchets (1-7) used a five-run fifth inning to break away from what had been shaping up as a pitchers duel, to secure the win over their Martin County foe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Washington Times Herald – Hatchets, Cougars Battle at Complex</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/news-and-links.bak/2007/2007-04-10-hatchets-cougars-battle-at-complex-washington-times-herald/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2007 12:07:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/news-and-links.bak/2007/2007-04-10-hatchets-cougars-battle-at-complex-washington-times-herald/</guid>
      <description>Hatchets, Cougars battle at Complex View Hatchets, Cougars battle at Complex PDF   Michelle Hulsey of Washington waits for a throw as a North Daviess runner breaks for second, in the Lady Cougars 6-2 win on Monday at the Sports Complex. Todd Lancaster | The Washington Times Herald   The North Daviess Cougars and the Washington Hatchet softball teams showed that softball played in early April can sometimes be just as interesting as the late May variety, as the Cougars and Hatchets kept each other on their collective heels for six innings on Monday at the Sports Complex.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Washington Times Herald – Drawing A Crowd</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/news-and-links.bak/2006/2006-07-21-washington-times-herald-drawing-a-crowd/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2006 12:10:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/news-and-links.bak/2006/2006-07-21-washington-times-herald-drawing-a-crowd/</guid>
      <description>Drawing a crowd      These Washington High School NJROTC cadets drew an attentive crowd while spending part of their summer vacation practicing in front of the Hatchet House at Bedford Road and Seventh Street on Thursday morning. Cadets (from left) are Adam Van Winkle and Adam Chestnut exchanging rifles. At right are cadets Christian Meyer and Ariza Miyasi. Watching in the foreground are (from left) Derek Bruce, Mike Hulsey and Cody Simmons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hatchets Fall at Sectional</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/news-and-links.bak/2006/2006-05-23-washington-times-herald-hatchets-fall-at-sectional/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2006 11:53:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/news-and-links.bak/2006/2006-05-23-washington-times-herald-hatchets-fall-at-sectional/</guid>
      <description>{{.Title}} {{if .Params.author}} — {{.Get &#34;Params.Author&#34; }} DeW{{end}} ### Hatchets fall at sectional View Hatchets fall at sectional PDF      Amber Criswell of Washington watches Whitney Hill (5) and Michelle Hulsey from the dugout at Pike Central on Monday. Todd Lancaster | Washington Times Herald   PETERSBURG — The Washington Hatchet softball team ended its season with a pair of bookend losses to Princeton.
The first loss came on Friday night and 72 hours later the Hatchets also dropped the Pike Central Sectional opener 13-0, to end a season that tallied just two wins, but showed improvement throughout the entire second half.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>