<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Corbin Harper on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</title>
    <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/people/corbin-harper/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Corbin Harper on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2013-{year} David E. Williams. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 01:01:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/people/corbin-harper/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 26, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-26-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 01:01:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-26-2019/</guid>
      <description>Lesa tossed and turned and coughed all night long and kept us both up. She&amp;#8217;s sick. Hope I don&amp;#8217;t get sick! Got up, got kids ready, took them to school. They acted like they were on vacation already and didn&amp;#8217;t want to get ready. Dillan spent 20 minutes in the shower that was supposed to be a rinse-off shower. Anyway, got them to school. Put Ashley&amp;#8217;s cheerleader bow in her hair in the school parking lot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 23, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-23-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 00:49:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-23-2019/</guid>
      <description>Went out deer hunting this morning, rained the entire time. Didn&amp;#8217;t see a thing but I heard some turkeys. Was supposed to pick up Bruce from Corbin&amp;#8217;s house around noon, then one or two, then they went to Bloomington, and I finally picked him up about three-thirty. They played X-Box, went to Captain D&amp;#8217;s for dinner, had meatloaf sandwiches for breakfast and toasted PBJs for lunch, stayed up late and slept in late.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 22, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-22-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 23:43:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-22-2019/</guid>
      <description>Friday! School, daycare, work. Left early, picked up kids, got a couple hours hunting in. Bruce rode the bus home with Corbin, Grady rides the same bus, because Bruce is spending the night at Corbin&amp;#8217;s. He&amp;#8217;s been excited all week and apparently he&amp;#8217;s a big kid now &amp;#8211; at least he&amp;#8217;s been acting like it. Emma was supposed to spend the night, came over awhile and did crafts with Ashley, they made a huge mess of the glitter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 16, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-16-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 22:15:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-16-2019/</guid>
      <description>Up before everyone, opening day deer season, out before light, then in at 11a, and out again at 3p until dark. Didn&amp;#8217;t see a thing other than squirrels! Ashley had a Girl Scout ecology event in Hoosier National Forest on opening day of all day! That scares me to death! She climbed the fire tower. That scares me to death too! She came back to us by the grace of God.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 5, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-5-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 04:06:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-5-2019/</guid>
      <description>Lesa and I woke up to my 8:00am alarm. Lesa got up, I tried to snooze more but unable. Kids were still asleep! Dogs rushed into Ashley&amp;#8217;s room and nuzzled her and she woke up, the boys followed. Even our dogs love the kids! Got the Cub Scout boys ready for selling popcorn, had to get mad and light a fire under them to get them moving. Bruce was his usual grumpy self, complained about everything.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>