<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mr. Hudson on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</title>
    <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/people/mr.-hudson/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mr. Hudson on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2013-{year} David E. Williams. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 23:21:06 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/people/mr.-hudson/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 5, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-5-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 23:21:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-5-2020/</guid>
      <description>Took kids to school, Dillan had his poster. Worked at SAIC all day. Bruce ate lunch in the office, Mr Hudson wasn&amp;#8217;t there, missed recess too. Stopped by PO Box on a whim and had two letters from Daniel, didn&amp;#8217;t get the usual notification I had mail. Picked up kids from daycare, nothing unusual there, Ashley upset she didn&amp;#8217;t get rewarded for cleaning up. Kind of cold outside so kids stayed in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 4, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-4-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 23:21:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-4-2020/</guid>
      <description>I took kids to the bus stop and came back home. Lesa and I both went to talk to Dwyane&amp;#8217;s Speech Therapist Darren Swango at Springville Elementary. Got to hear the kids announcements. Dwyane is doing really good, intermittent trouble with sh sounds. Afterward we talked about Dillan&amp;#8217;s speech, he can pronounce sounds okay but tends to go to fast, run words together, and kind of mumbles his words making him difficult to understand &amp;#8211; don&amp;#8217;t we know it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 3, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-3-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 23:56:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-3-2020/</guid>
      <description>Dropped kids at school. Went to work, Kind of a nerve-racking day. Really nice outside. Picked up kids, no major daycare issues to speak of, Bruce did get mouthy with Jessica so we talked about that. Dillan put hands on a kid at school and got called out for it by Mr Hudson. Kids played outside until dinner. Dillan said Ashley has a thing for his friend Bo from school so we teased her about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 15, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-15-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:22:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-15-2020/</guid>
      <description>Slept until 8 or so, kids started to make us breakfast in bed but we got up and requested breakfast at the table instead. That was sweet of them. Easy morning, was going to haul trash but that never happened. Kids did a lot of chores trying to earn tablet and computer time. Ashley and me took cookie money to Amanda and got more cookies. Had an issue with scheduling cookie booths but got that settled as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 31, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--january-31-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 00:01:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--january-31-2020/</guid>
      <description>Took kids to bus, cold and wet out. Got donuts for work, it was payday Friday. Picked up kids from daycare. Lesa went grocery shopping. Message on the answering machine from Mr Hudson, Bruce was in his office for smacking another kid on the butt. Brought home sushi for Ashley to try, she liked some of it but not all, Dillan and Bruce tried some too and both of them liked they said, I wound up finishing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 8, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-8-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 00:15:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-8-2020/</guid>
      <description>My day to take care of the sick kids again, got Dillan and Dwyane to the bus just fine. Let Ashley and Bruce sleep in late and when they did wake up I delivered software to SAIC, went to Dollar General to get some Gatorade for Bruce, and stopped by daycare and paid them. Got home, they didn&amp;#8217;t want breakfast, let them watch TV. Bruce threw up watching TV and got some on him and his blanket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 5, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-5-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 23:05:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-5-2019/</guid>
      <description>Work and school. Had a map meeting at 11:00am to discuss maps and map resources and didn&amp;#8217;t get out until 2:00pm! Lesa went to the dentist, got a clean and polish, no cavities. I got a text from Mrs Davis saying Ashley was in trouble and would have to sit out a game tonight, and that Mr Hudson would be calling me about it. Saw where I had a missed Springville call and called him back, he was in a meeting and would get back to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 5, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-5-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 04:06:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-5-2019/</guid>
      <description>Lesa and I woke up to my 8:00am alarm. Lesa got up, I tried to snooze more but unable. Kids were still asleep! Dogs rushed into Ashley&amp;#8217;s room and nuzzled her and she woke up, the boys followed. Even our dogs love the kids! Got the Cub Scout boys ready for selling popcorn, had to get mad and light a fire under them to get them moving. Bruce was his usual grumpy self, complained about everything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 3, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-3-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 23:01:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-3-2019/</guid>
      <description>My birthday, 58, an old man and feel it too, text from my dad, kids woke up trying to give me notes and presents, had to ask them to wait until evening during my party. Drove them to school again, called Mr Hudson and talked to him myself, got a good understanding of what happened, just kids being kids and parents (Kensie&amp;#8217;s) over-reacting. Lesa sent me chocolates at work for my birthday!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 2, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-2-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 22:36:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-2-2019/</guid>
      <description>Drove kids to school. Dwyane took a field trip to Spring Mill and had a picnic there, took a hike, visited the Grissom Space Center and played on the playground, according to Dwyane he had a great day. Mr Hudson talked to Kensie and Ashley again! Left a message on the machine but I didn&amp;#8217;t get to hear it because Lesa accidentally erased it. Lesa picked up Ashley from cheer practice, then picked up the boys from daycare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 1, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-1-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 23:39:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-1-2019/</guid>
      <description>Let boys ride bus, took Ashley to school. Left a message for Mr Hudson to call and fill me in on what actually happened but didn&amp;#8217;t return my call. Dillan had rash on his face now, all around his eyes, and he&amp;#8217;s been rubbing it, took a look and decided to call doctor for him too, Lesa was able to rearrange her work schedule to take him and then worked from home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 20, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-20-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 23:44:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-20-2019/</guid>
      <description>Friday, kids rode bus. Drove Suburban, miss is gone, fixed for $56, happy. Worked in Bloomington until 11:00, then drove disk to SAIC, tested and left for the day. Picked up Lesa, and we went to school for Grandparent&amp;#8217;s Day. As we walked in Mr Hudson intercepted us and pointed Dillan out sitting in the office, he hit Ashley in the back, and when he was told to stop, he got mad, threw a ball that hit a bucket that hit a girl in the mouth and busted her lip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 11, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-11-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 22:41:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-11-2019/</guid>
      <description>School, work. Mr Hudson called, Bruce got into a fight with a kid on the playground, started out friendly roughhousing that turned into to rough, had to go to his office and again during recess for remainder of the week. Ashley had cheerleader practice, Lesa picked her up, she did a couple of cheers for us. Dillan brought home a 32% on his school work and I got made and lectured him about it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>