<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Amanda Goen on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</title>
    <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/people/amanda-goen/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Amanda Goen on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2013-{year} David E. Williams. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:30:11 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/people/amanda-goen/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 12, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-12-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:30:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-12-2020/</guid>
      <description>School and work. Lots of COVID-19 talk everywhere, it&amp;#8217;s on everyone&amp;#8217;s mind, most people trying not to panic, some people are simply idiots. Wondering whether we should cancel our Spring Break trip, Lesa looking to me to keep us all safe, kids are blissfully unaware of the danger. Getting pressure to step up my game at work; the office is more than half empty. Ditto for Lesa&amp;#8217;s work, many people wanting to or already are working from home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 1, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-1-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 22:05:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-1-2020/</guid>
      <description>Skipped church, multiple people messaging wanting to know if we&amp;#8217;re okay &amp;#8211; we are. Slept until my Sunday alarm which hardly ever happens &amp;#8211; the kids or Lesa or the dogs almost always wake me up before. Ashley and me cooked breakfast for Lesa, Dwyane, and ourselves. Ashley, Dwyane, and myself played Yahtzee. Planned on doing something outdoors like hiking but it never happened. Kids rode bikes, Ashley and me mucked Oreo and Blackie&amp;#8217;s hutch, Lesa did some yard work so we were outdoors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 22, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-22-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 02:29:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-22-2020/</guid>
      <description>Got up at 9, amazing! Ashley made me eggs-in-a-basket and Lesa made me coffee, I am loved. Took Ashley to Johnny&amp;#8217;s Junction and handed her off to Amanda. They did a cookie booth at Kroger on South Walnut in Bloomington, and then they went to Wendy&amp;#8217;s for lunch, and then to Amanda&amp;#8217;s to drop off cookies, and then they went to World Thinking Day in Williams, Indiana. Sounds like she had a lot of fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 15, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-15-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:22:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-15-2020/</guid>
      <description>Slept until 8 or so, kids started to make us breakfast in bed but we got up and requested breakfast at the table instead. That was sweet of them. Easy morning, was going to haul trash but that never happened. Kids did a lot of chores trying to earn tablet and computer time. Ashley and me took cookie money to Amanda and got more cookies. Had an issue with scheduling cookie booths but got that settled as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 13, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-13-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 00:27:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-13-2020/</guid>
      <description>Got much colder, going to be single digits or worse overnight, worried about rabbits. Storm was supposed to hit us today but didn&amp;#8217;t, it went north of us instead. Kids stayed in truck until bus arrived. I got to work and just two of us there for the next hour. Ripped a couple of DVDs with tagged software and headed to SAIC. Spent the rest of the day there installing for EMI testing and have to go back in the morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 8, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-8-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 22:25:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-8-2020/</guid>
      <description>Woke up to snow on the ground. Super busy day. Took Ashley to Rural King to sell Girl Scout cookies at 10am, didn&amp;#8217;t sell a lot of cookies, would do much better at a grocery store I think. Came home and ate lunch and we all went to Dillan&amp;#8217;s basketball game, he is doing well, a little nervous and shooting the ball a bit hard and could use work dribbling but not bad for his first time playing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 14, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-14-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:34:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-14-2019/</guid>
      <description>Tried to sleep in, honest. Was awakened by Ashley and Bruce standing next to my side of the bed, in the dark, and they said: It&amp;#8217;s an emergency. Dwyane is bleeding from his eye. And I was awake just like that. So, they were chasing each other, and Dwyane tripped over some pillows, and hit his eye on Bruce&amp;#8217;s toy box. Goose egg on the forehead above his eyebrow, and a ¼&amp;#8221; cut on his eye lid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 21, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-21-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 00:21:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-21-2019/</guid>
      <description>School and work, school and work. Left early, picked up Ashley as a car-rider, daycare got the boys. Took Ashley to St. Vincent to cheer for the basketball games, we were early so hung out in the gym until things picked up. Meanwhile, Lesa picked up the boys. Girls team won their game 23 to 19. We left early because Ashley said she had a headache and wanted to go. When we left the boys were losing by 8 or 10 points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 12, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-12-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 22:53:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-12-2019/</guid>
      <description>School canceled. Lesa went in an hour late. I stayed home and kept the kids with me, didn&amp;#8217;t have it in me to drop them off at daycare. Ashley mostly watched TV and played with a doll, the boys played outside in the snow. Bruce came in and cried because his feet got too cold, got him warmed up, and put my heavy wool socks on him. Hot chocolate and some vegetable soup got them all warmed up again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 8, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-8-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 21:44:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-8-2019/</guid>
      <description>Dropped kids off at school, left off on time, and picked up kids. Lesa went grocery shopping after work so we beat her home. Kids played outside together and actually got along with each other. They are getting excited about going to the Smokies. Lesa took Girl Scout sales money to Amanda after we got the amount due calculated, I watched the kids and got them all in the shower. Ashley said she had a question, and told me that when she wiped she saw something crawling and she wanted me to look, so I did, and sure enough she had little white worms in her anus, took a sample with tweezers and looked them up, they are called thread or pin worms and can be treated with over-the-counter medicine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 5, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-5-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 04:06:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-5-2019/</guid>
      <description>Lesa and I woke up to my 8:00am alarm. Lesa got up, I tried to snooze more but unable. Kids were still asleep! Dogs rushed into Ashley&amp;#8217;s room and nuzzled her and she woke up, the boys followed. Even our dogs love the kids! Got the Cub Scout boys ready for selling popcorn, had to get mad and light a fire under them to get them moving. Bruce was his usual grumpy self, complained about everything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 22, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-22-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 00:41:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-22-2019/</guid>
      <description>Ashley&amp;#8217;s face much worse. Church, Junior Church with Ashley, Dwyane and Bruce. Dillan was in sanctuary with Lesa. Ashley sold lots of candy. Got Ashley a doctor appointment right after church so got her there right away, Prednisone alike last time, but this time tablets, and 20mg at that, made her get super hyper and hungry. Picked up a new GS order form from Amanda. Ate lunch at Taco Bell. At home tried to nap, guess I fell asleep for awhile, woke up and heard neighbor riding ATV around our loop again, Dillan and Bruce rode bikes through his yard and messed up his stone border.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 21, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-21-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 00:30:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-21-2019/</guid>
      <description>Scheduling hell, Lesa had girls day out with Andrea and Bobbie. I was supposed to go fishing and rent boat with Paul and Ross and kids. Ashley had a GS Horseback Riding event. Lesa canceled fishing for me after scheduling fishing for me. Anyway, Ashley woke up with allergic reaction on her face, called doctor, suggested Benadryl, didn&amp;#8217;t help like we knew it wouldn&amp;#8217;t. Got a plate for the 4Runner, chicken and rabbit feed, and took the kids to lunch at Steak &amp;#8216;n&amp;#8217; Shake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 29, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-29-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 22:02:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-29-2019/</guid>
      <description>Barely made the bus, Kim waited for the kids to get on board. Took an alternate, scenic route to work, highway under construction and down to one lane. Spent most of day doing research. Lesa having her own problems at work. Both of us pretty zoned out by the time we get home. Mrs. Davis texted us, Dillan punched William in the eye and got in trouble for it. I was none to happy!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>