<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ken and Cassie Tussey on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</title>
    <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/people/ken-and-cassie-tussey/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ken and Cassie Tussey on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2013-{year} David E. Williams. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 01:00:32 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/people/ken-and-cassie-tussey/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 28, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-28-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 01:00:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-28-2020/</guid>
      <description>Dropped kids at school, Bruce took his big helicopter for Show-and-Tell. Work. Took off late and went to the bank to deposit Girl Scout cookie checks, then Dollar General for Mt. Dews and antifreeze, losing 1&amp;frasl;2 a gallon a day, don&amp;#8217;t see a leak so it must be going out the tailpipe. Picked up kids from daycare. Lesa grocery shopped after work and we helped her carry in. Then everyone went into cleaning mode while Lesa got supper together &amp;#8211; we had pizza &amp;#8211; it is Friday night after all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 23, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-23-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 23:12:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-23-2020/</guid>
      <description>Up late last night, tired all day. Lesa kept letting the dogs in and out of the bedroom and I didn&amp;#8217;t even get to sleep until my alarm went off. Lesa stayed home from church, I was lockup deacon so we were the last ones out. Went home, got changed, and ate lunch. Dillan, Ashley, Bruce and myself went to the Tusseys. From there we went to Linda and Gordon Andersons&amp;#8217; house and picked up two huge turkeys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 6, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-6-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 23:57:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-6-2020/</guid>
      <description>Waited for the kids to get on the bus per usual. Ashley went on a field trip to the State House, she had a lot of fun. Picked the kids up from daycare, stopped at Dollar General to restock truck candy. At dinner Dillan recalled the time he went to the State House and him and Ashley sort of compared notes (tried to outdo each other), nothing too bad and mostly good-natured, Ashley does that a lot but this time Dillan was a bit jealous.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 31, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--january-31-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 00:01:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--january-31-2020/</guid>
      <description>Took kids to bus, cold and wet out. Got donuts for work, it was payday Friday. Picked up kids from daycare. Lesa went grocery shopping. Message on the answering machine from Mr Hudson, Bruce was in his office for smacking another kid on the butt. Brought home sushi for Ashley to try, she liked some of it but not all, Dillan and Bruce tried some too and both of them liked they said, I wound up finishing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 25, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-25-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 00:46:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-25-2020/</guid>
      <description>Got up and took care of everyone, Lesa sick, Dillan sick, Bruce sick, Dwyane half sick, Ashley okay and a big help! Missed the Beekeeping Seminar I was going to attend with Ken. Missed Dillan&amp;#8217;s first Courts for Christ basketball game. Made lunch. Did dishes. Did laundry. Made it to Ashley&amp;#8217;s first cookie booth, her share was 40 boxes sold! Made supper. Kids took showers. Played Sorry with boys and Lesa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 16, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-16-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 22:35:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-16-2020/</guid>
      <description>Bus stop, school, and daycare for the kids. Work and more work for the adults. Waited until last minute before leaving to get the kids. Lesa had supper ready per usual when we got home. Girl Scout meeting was canceled. I took Dillan to his first Courts for Christ basketball practice. Ashley went with, Lesa encouraged it. Lesa stayed home with boys doing I know not what. Dillan did okay for not having really played before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 31, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--december-31-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 02:01:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--december-31-2019/</guid>
      <description>New Year&amp;#8217;s Eve. Worked, both of us. Lesa got off early and got the place cleaned up. I worked a full day and picked up kids. Got home and we all went into overdrive cleaning and picking up, well maybe not Bruce. Ken and Cassie Tussey, Emma and Woodrow came over to eat pizza, and they brought venison sausage with them! We played several games of euchre while kids played and ultimately watched TV.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 7, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-7-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 23:58:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-7-2019/</guid>
      <description>Slept until 8am, surprised at that. Stopped by PO Box and picked up another letter from Daniel om my way to take the kids to get hair cuts at Fantastic Sams. The boys wanted their hair cut short so we did the #4 on top and #2 on side summer cut. Ashley wanted bangs, stylist checked and said it wouldn&amp;#8217;t work very well, so she got her ends trimmed as originally planned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 22, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-22-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 23:43:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-22-2019/</guid>
      <description>Friday! School, daycare, work. Left early, picked up kids, got a couple hours hunting in. Bruce rode the bus home with Corbin, Grady rides the same bus, because Bruce is spending the night at Corbin&amp;#8217;s. He&amp;#8217;s been excited all week and apparently he&amp;#8217;s a big kid now &amp;#8211; at least he&amp;#8217;s been acting like it. Emma was supposed to spend the night, came over awhile and did crafts with Ashley, they made a huge mess of the glitter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 26, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-26-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2019 23:53:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-26-2019/</guid>
      <description>Rained pretty heavy all night and most of the day. Got up at 8a, took Dillan to guitar lesson and picked up Ashley. During lesson, Cassie, Emma, Woodrow, Ashley and myself went to Emma Miracle&amp;#8217;s to see the baby goats. Came home and Ashley very tired but won&amp;#8217;t nap. Ate lunch. Went to Rural King, got some stuff for the rabbits and chickens. Went to Walmart and got Ashley a pair of dress shoes and a pair of dress boots, got Dillan a new pair of mud boots, and Dwyane a pair of dress shoes as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 25, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-25-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 23:41:18 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-25-2019/</guid>
      <description>Took kids to school, Ashley going home with Cassie and Emma Tussey tonight after school, so checked her overnight bag and wrote a note so Cassie could get her. Dillan and the boys went to daycare. I wound up at Atterbury all day and didn&amp;#8217;t get home until after six. Lesa went grocery shopping, then picked up the boys. She dropped Dillan off at church for C3 Nerf Wars, Dillan was pissed because Ken used a paint gun and it hurt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 24, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-24-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 23:34:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-24-2019/</guid>
      <description>Dropped kids off at school. Went to Scientia, expected to go to Atterbury today but stayed to help a co-worker. Worker until 4:30p and then left to get kids from daycare. They had a little time to play before eating and after dinner played some more. The kids had some homework, Bruce sight words, Dwyane reading, Ashley reading, and Dillan spelling. Ashley got all her stuff ready for spending the night at Emma&amp;#8217;s tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 22, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-22-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 23:58:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-22-2019/</guid>
      <description>Took kids to school. Dropped truck off at Sturgis and had left front wheel bearing replaced. Worked at Scientia until 2p, luckily I wasn&amp;#8217;t need out at Camp Atterbury so I got to pick Ashley up from school. The boys rode the van to daycare per usual. I took Ashley to her first real cheerleading event for Springville Elementary at an away game. The girl and boy Basketball teams played Heltonville.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 20, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-20-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 00:06:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-20-2019/</guid>
      <description>Cincinnati Christian Church 100th Anniversary and they had a lunch and celebration, drew a huge crowd, all the deacons showed up at 9 and parked at library across the street. Ashley and Dillan came in early with me. Stayed for lunch and while kids played nine square outside we listened to some of the older folks stories about the church. It was kind of nice. Came home, kids played outside. Kaleena called, Ashley went to her house and the two of them showed up later at our house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 19, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-19-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2019 22:33:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-19-2019/</guid>
      <description>Got up early, Ashley and me went to the Tussey&amp;#8217;s along with Nicole Rogers. We slaughtered and butchered 30 chickens. Ashley and Emma helped. Emma got kicked by their donkey but is okay. Ashley did all stations except butchering and killing. Came home with a cooler full of meat birds. Dillan was riding dirt bike when we got home and the boys were riding bicycles. After showers Ashley joined the boys and I took a nap, Lesa went and got 20 pounds of ice to put on the birds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 17, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-17-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 23:14:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-17-2019/</guid>
      <description>Back to work for me, Lesa stayed home, kids went to daycare. Long, long day for everyone I think. Bruce aggravated Dillan at daycare, Dillan kicked Bruce and hurt him. Annetta called and said Bruce wasn&amp;#8217;t behaving his normal self, wouldn&amp;#8217;t eat, and just sat holding his side. He said it hurt really bad so she called me. She didn&amp;#8217;t think I needed to leave work early so I didn&amp;#8217;t. Lesa came up and we returned the rental.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 10, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-10-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 23:26:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-10-2019/</guid>
      <description>Kids glad I got them ready for school this morning, they love Lesa but yesterday was a departure from their normal routine. Dropped them off at school and headed to work. Thought I&amp;#8217;d be heading back to Atterbury but not, probably tomorrow. It&amp;#8217;s Thursday, which is $5 sushi day at Fresh Tyme, so I got some sushi for lunch. Left at 3:30p and made it just in time for Parent-Teacher Conferences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 6, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-6-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 22:31:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-6-2019/</guid>
      <description>Stayed home from church, everyone utterly exhausted, especially Lesa. Leisurely morning. I picked up Ashley at 12:30p and she was ready to come home. They got wet, no fly on the tent, and when it began raining they just threw the fly on top but the girls had a good time. I took Dillan to his guitar lesson at 2p, Ken revealed to Dillan the top 4, or was it 5, secrets of being a guitar player.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 17, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-17-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2019 23:47:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-17-2019/</guid>
      <description>Took Dillan to his first guitar lesson by Ken Tussey, Dillan didn&amp;rsquo;t offer much feedback. Picked up 6 fryers, fixed up brooder coop, Rural King for supplies. Got a little rain. Dillan played at Gabe&amp;rsquo;s. Everybody fighting, Lesa and Ashley going at it, I&amp;rsquo;m the bad guy always. Baths.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 10, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-10-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 23:37:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-10-2019/</guid>
      <description>Kind of slept in, hauled trash, Lowe&amp;#8217;s for rabbit playpen materials. Tried fixing leaky shower drain, couldn&amp;#8217;t find supplies. Started building playpen with Ashley. Cub Scout End of Summer Pool Party, Ashley invited Emma, thought she would spend night but didn&amp;#8217;t. Everyone had fun!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 3, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-3-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 22:28:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-3-2019/</guid>
      <description>Slept in, kids sitting quietly in living room, first time ever. Ashley bridged from Brownie to Junior, it was nice. Boys rode bikes and played while Lesa and Ashley ordered school cloths. Water main broke. Nicole&amp;#8217;s, slaughtered Ken Tussey&amp;#8217;s meat chickens. Tacos, TV, showers, bed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>