<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Elahdy Smith on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</title>
    <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/people/elahdy-smith/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Elahdy Smith on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2013-{year} David E. Williams. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 22:35:18 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/people/elahdy-smith/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 16, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-16-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 22:35:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-16-2020/</guid>
      <description>Bus stop, school, and daycare for the kids. Work and more work for the adults. Waited until last minute before leaving to get the kids. Lesa had supper ready per usual when we got home. Girl Scout meeting was canceled. I took Dillan to his first Courts for Christ basketball practice. Ashley went with, Lesa encouraged it. Lesa stayed home with boys doing I know not what. Dillan did okay for not having really played before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 2, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-2-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:02:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-2-2019/</guid>
      <description>Back to work and school. We suffered today. I picked up the mail from the PO Box, another letter from Daniel. Same old, same old. How he&amp;#8217;s sorry, how he loves the kids so much, how he wishes the kids would forgive him and write back. He pretends he cares about the kids, pretends to be sorry, but in reality his letters are all about him. We see typical addict behavior and mentality and we suspect the sudden burst of letters has to do with a program of some sort and he&amp;#8217;s hoping to gain an early release or something.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>