<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nicole Rogers on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</title>
    <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/people/nicole-rogers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nicole Rogers on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2013-{year} David E. Williams. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 23:49:49 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/people/nicole-rogers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 24, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-24-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 23:49:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-24-2020/</guid>
      <description>Rainy days and Mondays. Got kids to school okay. Went to SAIC, stayed all day. I&amp;#8217;m sick, have a cold, my nose is runny and my head stopped up, being sick sucks. Left SAIC early and picked up kids from school and headed home and took a nap while the kids watched TV. Lesa got home and we ate supper. The boys had a Pack meeting, Bruce did a skit with his den mates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 19, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-19-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2019 22:33:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-19-2019/</guid>
      <description>Got up early, Ashley and me went to the Tussey&amp;#8217;s along with Nicole Rogers. We slaughtered and butchered 30 chickens. Ashley and Emma helped. Emma got kicked by their donkey but is okay. Ashley did all stations except butchering and killing. Came home with a cooler full of meat birds. Dillan was riding dirt bike when we got home and the boys were riding bicycles. After showers Ashley joined the boys and I took a nap, Lesa went and got 20 pounds of ice to put on the birds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 17, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-17-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 23:14:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-17-2019/</guid>
      <description>Back to work for me, Lesa stayed home, kids went to daycare. Long, long day for everyone I think. Bruce aggravated Dillan at daycare, Dillan kicked Bruce and hurt him. Annetta called and said Bruce wasn&amp;#8217;t behaving his normal self, wouldn&amp;#8217;t eat, and just sat holding his side. He said it hurt really bad so she called me. She didn&amp;#8217;t think I needed to leave work early so I didn&amp;#8217;t. Lesa came up and we returned the rental.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 24, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-24-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 00:28:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-24-2019/</guid>
      <description>Woke up to kids screaming and putting their hands on each other &amp;#8211; idiot, stupid, butt head, etc. Grounded all of them from screens of all types for entire weekend: no TV, tablets, phones, YouTube on computer, clock on microwave, etc. It was like we sentenced them to hell judging by all the wails, moans and groans we received. Went to Rural King and bought Ashley&amp;#8217;s pet play area, would be great for chickens, will be used for rabbits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 3, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-3-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 22:28:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-3-2019/</guid>
      <description>Slept in, kids sitting quietly in living room, first time ever. Ashley bridged from Brownie to Junior, it was nice. Boys rode bikes and played while Lesa and Ashley ordered school cloths. Water main broke. Nicole&amp;#8217;s, slaughtered Ken Tussey&amp;#8217;s meat chickens. Tacos, TV, showers, bed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>