<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Daniel on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</title>
    <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/people/daniel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Daniel on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2013-{year} David E. Williams. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:50:58 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/people/daniel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 19, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-19-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:50:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-19-2020/</guid>
      <description>Ate breakfast with the family and then I went to work. Started at SAIC and then headed to Scientia, just two of us in the office, worked a 9-hour day. One of my co-workers was hospitalized with COVID-19 symptoms and difficulty breathing, scary sh*t. Picked up another letter from Daniel. Lesa worked from home and watched the kids. Sounds like it went mostly okay. Ashley said she didn&amp;#8217;t fight with Lesa at all, Lesa didn&amp;#8217;t say otherwise so proud of both of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 5, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-5-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 23:21:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-5-2020/</guid>
      <description>Took kids to school, Dillan had his poster. Worked at SAIC all day. Bruce ate lunch in the office, Mr Hudson wasn&amp;#8217;t there, missed recess too. Stopped by PO Box on a whim and had two letters from Daniel, didn&amp;#8217;t get the usual notification I had mail. Picked up kids from daycare, nothing unusual there, Ashley upset she didn&amp;#8217;t get rewarded for cleaning up. Kind of cold outside so kids stayed in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 20, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-20-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:16:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-20-2020/</guid>
      <description>Martin Luther King Junior Day and Lesa and I had off. The kids had school to make up a snow day so we were kid-free. I got up and got kids ready for school and took them to the bus stop. I went back to bed and slept all morning! Got up, we took showers, and went to Bloomington for lunch. We went to Asuka Japanese Steakhouse, Sushi &amp;amp; Noodles and did the Hibachi, first time experience for us, we had steak and shrimp with fried rice, and soup prior.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 3, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-3-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2020 01:44:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-3-2020/</guid>
      <description>Work and daycare. Dropped kids off and headed to work. Lesa and I texted back-and-forth on how to handle Ashley&amp;#8217;s Cookie Rally at Stalker. Ended up Lesa went grocery shopping and she picked up a couple of pizzas from Springville Store while I picked up the kids from daycare, I needed to get gas so did that first. Jessica said she had issues with Bruce but the other kids did okay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 20, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-20-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 00:37:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-20-2019/</guid>
      <description>School, daycare, work. Lesa had a long rough day of moving and network being out &amp;#8211; per usual. I had an okay workday but couldn&amp;#8217;t wait to get out of there. Kids had a fun day of partying at school, Polar Express day where they wore their pajamas and watched the movie, a scavenger hunt, and other festivities to kick off Christmas Break. I left work at 3:30pm and went to get kids, picked up a card Daniel sent to our PO Box, picked up Papa John&amp;#8217;s pizza, and filled my tank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 5, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-5-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 22:56:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-5-2019/</guid>
      <description>Election Day, no school, dropped kids off at daycare. Received email overnight that mail had arrived at the PO Box so I went and got it after dropping them off. Had five letters all from Daniel with each one directed to the kids. The dates were Oct. 2, 10, 18, 25 and Nov. 1. I worked in Bloomington and tied to get access to NGA maps, submitted request and awaiting the Need-to-Know confirmation from Navy sponsor.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>