<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Paul and Andrea Fries on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</title>
    <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/people/paul-and-andrea-fries/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Paul and Andrea Fries on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2013-{year} David E. Williams. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 22:21:36 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/people/paul-and-andrea-fries/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 22, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-22-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 22:21:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-22-2020/</guid>
      <description>Church was live-streamed although we didn&amp;#8217;t watch. Instead we did our own church, sang songs, and Lesa had a lesson for us. It worked out pretty good. Made it to Lowe&amp;#8217;s and got the right faucet. I went to Aldi&amp;#8217;s looking for TP, milk, pizza rolls, chicken tenders, and mashed potatoes &amp;#8211; had nada. Went to Walmart and they had everything but the mashed potatoes. Got home and fixed the faucet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 20, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-20-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 00:37:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-20-2019/</guid>
      <description>School, daycare, work. Lesa had a long rough day of moving and network being out &amp;#8211; per usual. I had an okay workday but couldn&amp;#8217;t wait to get out of there. Kids had a fun day of partying at school, Polar Express day where they wore their pajamas and watched the movie, a scavenger hunt, and other festivities to kick off Christmas Break. I left work at 3:30pm and went to get kids, picked up a card Daniel sent to our PO Box, picked up Papa John&amp;#8217;s pizza, and filled my tank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 10, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-10-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 23:28:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-10-2019/</guid>
      <description>Church, Deacon in Back and Lobby Security. Afterward, we hooked up trailer and loaded bikes, got gas, and went to Paul and Andrea&amp;#8217;s for lunch with the Johnsons. Beautiful day for cookout. Kids rode bikes and had an awesome time and didn&amp;#8217;t want to leave. Got home and kids still rambunctious and played outside. Kaleena came over and ate with us. I got into a fight with Lesa and left for a couple of hours, had to decide whether I wanted to come back or not, came back for the kids&amp;#8217; sake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 27, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-27-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2019 22:35:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-27-2019/</guid>
      <description>Church, paid for Dillan and Ashley to go to SuperStart. Lesa got mad at Dillan and me for horsing in the pews during the sermon. Ross and Bobbi Johnson&amp;#8217;s last day, most likely won&amp;#8217;t see them again. They gave kids some Matchbox toy cars. We took them and the Fries out to lunch at El Ranchero Mexican Restaurant in Bloomington, we all had a nice time &amp;#8211; even the kids. Always hard to lose good friends and decent people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 21, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-21-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 00:30:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-21-2019/</guid>
      <description>Scheduling hell, Lesa had girls day out with Andrea and Bobbie. I was supposed to go fishing and rent boat with Paul and Ross and kids. Ashley had a GS Horseback Riding event. Lesa canceled fishing for me after scheduling fishing for me. Anyway, Ashley woke up with allergic reaction on her face, called doctor, suggested Benadryl, didn&amp;#8217;t help like we knew it wouldn&amp;#8217;t. Got a plate for the 4Runner, chicken and rabbit feed, and took the kids to lunch at Steak &amp;#8216;n&amp;#8217; Shake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 11, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-11-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2019 22:59:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-11-2019/</guid>
      <description>Church. I baptized Ashley and Dillan! Praise God! How awesome is that‽ We took Kathy Mitchell and Paul and Andrea Fries to El Ranchero for lunch, we all had a great time! Fantastic Sams for kid haircuts. Bought Lesa bedroom suite/mattress at Living Room Center. Truck overheating.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>