<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jessica Smith on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</title>
    <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/people/jessica-smith/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jessica Smith on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2013-{year} David E. Williams. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 23:19:04 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/people/jessica-smith/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 13, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-13-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 23:19:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-13-2020/</guid>
      <description>School and work. Had a hard time getting motivated at work. Was going to leave early but wound up staying later. School robocalled to say school is closed due to COVID-19 and won&amp;#8217;t be open until April. When I picked up kids I talked to Jessica about what we could expect daycare to do and it looks like unless sickness hits them it will be an option for us. Both our workplaces are being flexible so I think we&amp;#8217;ll be okay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 3, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-3-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2020 01:44:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-3-2020/</guid>
      <description>Work and daycare. Dropped kids off and headed to work. Lesa and I texted back-and-forth on how to handle Ashley&amp;#8217;s Cookie Rally at Stalker. Ended up Lesa went grocery shopping and she picked up a couple of pizzas from Springville Store while I picked up the kids from daycare, I needed to get gas so did that first. Jessica said she had issues with Bruce but the other kids did okay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 20, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-20-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 21:04:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-20-2019/</guid>
      <description>Kids school, Lesa and me went to work. Dropped off Girl Scout destined for daycare before work. Got another letter from Daniel dated November 12 and scanned and added it to site. Picked up kids from daycare. Talked to Annetta and Jessica for quite awhile about school closings. Ashley told them we&amp;#8217;re going to go to a different school so naturally they were wondering about our kids. Dillan told me I was a good dad, better than his birth dad, because I love and take care of him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 5, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-5-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 22:56:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-5-2019/</guid>
      <description>Election Day, no school, dropped kids off at daycare. Received email overnight that mail had arrived at the PO Box so I went and got it after dropping them off. Had five letters all from Daniel with each one directed to the kids. The dates were Oct. 2, 10, 18, 25 and Nov. 1. I worked in Bloomington and tied to get access to NGA maps, submitted request and awaiting the Need-to-Know confirmation from Navy sponsor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 30, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-30-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 22:42:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-30-2019/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217;s Friday and Labor Day weekend, we get Monday off. Totally missed the bus, dropped kids off at school. Payday Friday, so I bought donuts for the shop per usual. Long, long day! Got off work at 3:00p and even gave them an extra hour. Took long leisurely drive through the countryside to pick up kids, truck started having transmission problems half way there, didn&amp;#8217;t want to pull or kick down into lower gear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 1, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-1-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 23:56:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-1-2019/</guid>
      <description>Caught raccoon in live-trap again. Daycare, Jessica&amp;#8217;s pool. Dr Hoff called, no blood in urine, PSA went from 4.6 to 1.6, follow-up January, every 6 months thereafter. It&amp;#8217;s great news, on Tuesday I had 5 year expectancy. Lesa took boys to last night of swim lessons, passed, party!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>