<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mrs. Thompson on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</title>
    <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/people/mrs.-thompson/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mrs. Thompson on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2013-{year} David E. Williams. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 23:58:29 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/people/mrs.-thompson/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 7, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-7-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 23:58:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-7-2019/</guid>
      <description>Slept until 8am, surprised at that. Stopped by PO Box and picked up another letter from Daniel om my way to take the kids to get hair cuts at Fantastic Sams. The boys wanted their hair cut short so we did the #4 on top and #2 on side summer cut. Ashley wanted bangs, stylist checked and said it wouldn&amp;#8217;t work very well, so she got her ends trimmed as originally planned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 2, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-2-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 00:02:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-2-2019/</guid>
      <description>Back to work and school. We suffered today. I picked up the mail from the PO Box, another letter from Daniel. Same old, same old. How he&amp;#8217;s sorry, how he loves the kids so much, how he wishes the kids would forgive him and write back. He pretends he cares about the kids, pretends to be sorry, but in reality his letters are all about him. We see typical addict behavior and mentality and we suspect the sudden burst of letters has to do with a program of some sort and he&amp;#8217;s hoping to gain an early release or something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 29, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-29-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 22:02:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-29-2019/</guid>
      <description>Barely made the bus, Kim waited for the kids to get on board. Took an alternate, scenic route to work, highway under construction and down to one lane. Spent most of day doing research. Lesa having her own problems at work. Both of us pretty zoned out by the time we get home. Mrs. Davis texted us, Dillan punched William in the eye and got in trouble for it. I was none to happy!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>