<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Maelee on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</title>
    <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/people/maelee/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Maelee on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2013-{year} David E. Williams. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 00:27:56 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/people/maelee/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 28, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-28-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 00:27:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-28-2019/</guid>
      <description>Easy morning, got woke by kids, but not too early. Kids played with toys but Lesa had to put them outside, they were just too rowdy. She packed some sandwiches and at noon we headed to Sarah and Kaleigh&amp;#8217;s for the Williams Christmas. Two hours later we arrived, right on time. Becky and Maelee and boys already there, my parents and brother came shortly after. Kids had a great time, we had a good time too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 30, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-30-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 22:52:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-30-2019/</guid>
      <description>Williams Thanksgiving today. Nasty rainy day all day. Lesa had a lot of cooking going on so I took the kids to Starbucks to get hot chocolate and mostly to get then out of her hair. Then we went to Walmart and got a couple of items Lesa needed like dinner rolls and celery. Skipped the donuts even though it was tempting. First to show was Sarah and Kaleigh followed by Becky and kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 29, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-29-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 23:40:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-29-2019/</guid>
      <description>Got up before daylight and went deer hunting, Didn&amp;#8217;t see anything. Got in and Lesa frustrated with kids but trying hard. Ashley busy cleaning her room and making it safe for Maelee. Boys have a mess absolutely everywhere. Spent part of the day cleaning up the house, yard and deck. After lunch Lesa went grocery shopping and kids got tablets for the chores they did. Lesa got home with the ingredients we needed to make deserts for tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 26, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-26-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 01:01:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-26-2019/</guid>
      <description>Lesa tossed and turned and coughed all night long and kept us both up. She&amp;#8217;s sick. Hope I don&amp;#8217;t get sick! Got up, got kids ready, took them to school. They acted like they were on vacation already and didn&amp;#8217;t want to get ready. Dillan spent 20 minutes in the shower that was supposed to be a rinse-off shower. Anyway, got them to school. Put Ashley&amp;#8217;s cheerleader bow in her hair in the school parking lot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 19, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-19-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 23:00:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-19-2019/</guid>
      <description>School and work, rained all day, slow-ish day for me, not sure about Lesa. Left at 4:30 and got the kids on the late side but I don&amp;#8217;t think they noticed &amp;#8211; they were watching TV. Got home and no place to go! Checked rabbits with Ashley, boys played, a little bit of homework with Lesa, Ashley read for an hour and then Maelee-proofed her room for Thanksgiving. Boys took baths, Dillan a shower.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>