<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Annetta Starr on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</title>
    <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/people/annetta-starr/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Annetta Starr on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2013-{year} David E. Williams. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 22:48:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/people/annetta-starr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 16, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-16-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 22:48:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-16-2020/</guid>
      <description>Bizarre day to say the least. Lesa went into work. I got kids ready and took them to daycare and then I went into work. Not many people at work, one co-worker came in, said he didn&amp;#8217;t feel well, and left. Two others left midday leaving me by myself. I worked a full day and then picked up the kids. Annetta said they were all good and the next time they&amp;#8217;re at daycare she&amp;#8217;ll get them some ice cream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 21, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-21-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 23:59:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-21-2020/</guid>
      <description>The kids pissed me off so bad this morning. They are total butts! I sent them into school without a hug or kiss. First time I&amp;#8217;ve ever done that. Worked at SAIC all day, it sucked. I didn&amp;#8217;t want to pick the kids up come quitting time. First time I&amp;#8217;ve felt that way too. Asked Annetta what she would charge me to take them for the entire weekend. Stopped by TK, turned in paperwork and left a deposit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 30, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-30-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 23:45:40 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-30-2019/</guid>
      <description>New Year&amp;#8217;s Eve Eve. Work and daycare, both sucked. Picked kids up and got an earful about the kids&amp;#8217; behavior. Dillan and Ashley fighting over a chair, Ashley scratched and drew blood, Dillan pinched and caused a welt, both told to sit and Dillan went off about how he hates it at daycare and started kicking a chair around. Bruce mouthed off at Annetta and got a timeout for that. Ashley and Dwyane fighting over a pillow, Dwyane throwing it in the bathroom and Ashley hitting him for doing it, multiple times, each trying to outdo the other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 20, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-20-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 21:04:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-20-2019/</guid>
      <description>Kids school, Lesa and me went to work. Dropped off Girl Scout destined for daycare before work. Got another letter from Daniel dated November 12 and scanned and added it to site. Picked up kids from daycare. Talked to Annetta and Jessica for quite awhile about school closings. Ashley told them we&amp;#8217;re going to go to a different school so naturally they were wondering about our kids. Dillan told me I was a good dad, better than his birth dad, because I love and take care of him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 17, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-17-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 23:14:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-17-2019/</guid>
      <description>Back to work for me, Lesa stayed home, kids went to daycare. Long, long day for everyone I think. Bruce aggravated Dillan at daycare, Dillan kicked Bruce and hurt him. Annetta called and said Bruce wasn&amp;#8217;t behaving his normal self, wouldn&amp;#8217;t eat, and just sat holding his side. He said it hurt really bad so she called me. She didn&amp;#8217;t think I needed to leave work early so I didn&amp;#8217;t. Lesa came up and we returned the rental.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 30, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-30-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 22:42:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-30-2019/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217;s Friday and Labor Day weekend, we get Monday off. Totally missed the bus, dropped kids off at school. Payday Friday, so I bought donuts for the shop per usual. Long, long day! Got off work at 3:00p and even gave them an extra hour. Took long leisurely drive through the countryside to pick up kids, truck started having transmission problems half way there, didn&amp;#8217;t want to pull or kick down into lower gear.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>