<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gary Flynn on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</title>
    <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/people/gary-flynn/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gary Flynn on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2013-{year} David E. Williams. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 00:41:43 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/people/gary-flynn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 22, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-22-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 00:41:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-22-2019/</guid>
      <description>Ashley&amp;#8217;s face much worse. Church, Junior Church with Ashley, Dwyane and Bruce. Dillan was in sanctuary with Lesa. Ashley sold lots of candy. Got Ashley a doctor appointment right after church so got her there right away, Prednisone alike last time, but this time tablets, and 20mg at that, made her get super hyper and hungry. Picked up a new GS order form from Amanda. Ate lunch at Taco Bell. At home tried to nap, guess I fell asleep for awhile, woke up and heard neighbor riding ATV around our loop again, Dillan and Bruce rode bikes through his yard and messed up his stone border.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 15, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-15-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 23:03:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-15-2019/</guid>
      <description>Church, lead deacon in back, security also. After church went to work and picked up Toyota 4-Runner I bought off Todd Davidson. Lesa followed me in Suburban and kids rode with me, they were excited to ride in something new and were amazed at the stick shift. Ashley went to Kaleena&amp;#8217;s and Dillan to Gabe&amp;#8217;s. Gary Flynn&amp;#8217;s son and grandson were riding their motorcycles around our loop, Dillan called them butt holes, whole thing exploded into an argument but sort of smoothed over but not really resolved.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>