<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Joshua on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</title>
    <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/tags/joshua/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Joshua on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2013-{year} David E. Williams. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 07:10:35 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/tags/joshua/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Washington to graduate 182 Saturday – Washington Times Herald</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/news-and-links/2017/2017-05-26-washington-times-herald-washington-to-graduate-182-saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 07:10:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/news-and-links/2017/2017-05-26-washington-times-herald-washington-to-graduate-182-saturday/</guid>
      <description>Special to TH. Friday, May 26, 2017 7:00 AM
Washington to graduate 182 Saturday. Washington Times Herald.
Retrieved from http://www.washtimesherald.com/ Washington to graduate 182 Saturday Washington High School will present diplomas to 182 graduates during its commencement exercises at 2 p.m. Saturday in the high school gymnasium.
Following the processional, Calie Garland will open the ceremony after which the NJROTC will present the colors and the choirs will lead the national anthem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paying it forward – Washington Times Herald</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/news-and-links/2015/2015-04-30-washington-times-herald-paying-it-forward/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2015 07:00:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/news-and-links/2015/2015-04-30-washington-times-herald-paying-it-forward/</guid>
      <description>Lindsay Owens. Thursday, April 30, 2015 7:00 AM.
Paying it forward. Washington Times Herald.
Retrieved from http://www.washtimesherald.com/ Paying it forward WHS students doing good deeds for those in need
Washington High School students in Barb Knepp’s health classes have joined with students involved in Choice for Change, a student group working to create a more positive atmosphere at WHS, to pay it forward throughout the month of May.
Participating students will receive three “Pay It Forward” cards and are asked to do three nice things for people in the community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning to save lives – Washington Times Herald</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/news-and-links/2015/2015-03-30-washington-times-herald-learning-to-save-lives/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2015 14:25:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/news-and-links/2015/2015-03-30-washington-times-herald-learning-to-save-lives/</guid>
      <description>Lindsay Owens. Monday, March 30, 2015 2:25 PM.
Learning to save lives. Washington Times Herald.
Retrieved from http://www.washtimesherald.com/  * *  Joshua Hulsey practices on a CPR dummy during health class at Washington High School. Kelly Overton | Times Herald
Students required to learn CPR Students in health classes at Washington High School have spent the days leading up to spring break learning something that could impact lives forever, CPR.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Washington High School Honor Roll – The Washington Times-Herald</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/news-and-links/2014/2014-06-11-washington-times-herald-washington-high-school-honor-roll/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2014 14:50:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/news-and-links/2014/2014-06-11-washington-times-herald-washington-high-school-honor-roll/</guid>
      <description>Washington High School honor roll Wednesday, Jun 11, 2014 2:50 AM | The Washington Times-Herald Washington High School 2nd semester honor roll
Freshmen
&amp;#8230;
Honor Roll 2.75+, No Grade Below C-: Logan Allen, Emma Andis, Jennifer Angeles, Sandra Barco, Jessica Basham, Logan Bateman, Fabian Becerra, Cheyenne Bene, Austin Boyd, Alexis Brown, Julian Brown, Katie Burress, Paula Clark, Chase Clymer, Nataly Delgado, Ariel DeMotte, Eben Duncan, Michael Duncan, Reed Edwards, Jada Faith, Daniel Flores-Serrano, Austin Fox, Felicity Fox, Sheylyn Fox, Rayven Graber, Callie Gray, Lillian Harman, Makenzie Healy, Douglas Heidenreich, Mallory Heller, Mallory Hill, Zachary Hinkle, Alexis Hornback, Ian Howard, Joshua Hulsey, Tianna Inmon, Adriana Kennedy, Alyssa Knepp, Jordan Kunkel, Benjamin Lambert, Alexandra Lamb, Max Lancaster, Donovan Langdon, Kyrie Lundy, Stephen Mason, Ian Matteson, Lucas Mattes, Katherine Matthews, Mykell Miller, Karla Miranda, Austin Moody, Madison Murphy, Noah Myers, Reid Neff, Jacob Overton, Brandon Pitcher, Alexa Rayman, Michaele Rhodes, Caitlyn Riester, Dillon Roark, Brisia Rodriguez, Guadalupe Sandoval, Gissele Santos, Jaylin Schaller, Wesley Shelton, Stephen Sievers, Christina Smith, Elizabeth Smith, Lakeysha Sullivan, Justin Tedrow, Mathew Trueblood, Jackson Wade, Allyson Weis, Izabella Wells, Mara White, Aaron Wilson, Michael Yates</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>