<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gabriel and Gracie Clark on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</title>
    <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/people/gabriel-and-gracie-clark/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gabriel and Gracie Clark on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2013-{year} David E. Williams. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:01:59 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/people/gabriel-and-gracie-clark/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 19, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-19-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:01:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-19-2020/</guid>
      <description>Church, I taught in Junior Church as well. Kids glad I was there and the boys hung out with me. They love us so much it&amp;#8217;s hard to fathom sometimes. After church, Shane Schroyer came out and checked our furnace, it was acting kind of odd a few weeks ago but seems to be okay. Bruce and then Dillan hung out with us to watch. After Shane left we had lunch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 5, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-5-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 00:55:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-5-2020/</guid>
      <description>Church, Family Sunday, combined Sunday School, Dillan still at Gabe&amp;#8217;s and didn&amp;#8217;t go to church with us. Kids played, and we had Dillan home by two. Went to Walmart and let the kids get some toys or in Ashley&amp;#8217;s case some toys and crafts, with their Christmas money and gift cards. Thirty dollars each and they enjoyed even if we didn&amp;#8217;t so much. Got home and kids played rest of the afternoon, Bruce was exercising his imagination some which was refreshing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 4, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-4-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 00:30:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-4-2020/</guid>
      <description>Kids woke us of course. Fought with each other of course. Drove us crazy of course. Wouldn&amp;#8217;t listen to us of course. Talked back to us of course. Boys played. Ashley played. Lesa worked. I tried to sleep. Lesa fixed up Ashley&amp;#8217;s Girl Scout vest. I took Dillan to Dunham&amp;#8217;s Sports and bought him basketball shoes, shorts, pants and jacket, protector, and a basketball (to be shared), he starts basketball practice with Courts for Christ next week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – January 1, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-1-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 23:36:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/01/status-update--january-1-2020/</guid>
      <description>Kids woke us up, I sent them to their rooms and told them to be quiet. Went back to bed and to sleep. Lesa got up and kept things quiet. I slept until 10am! Longest in almost 6 years unless sick. It was awesome. Lesa made me coffee which was nice. I played Battleship with Ashley, then Dwyane. Took Dwyane to Mrs Dillman&amp;#8217;s house, her grandson Jay invited Dwyane to spend the night and go to Urban Air with them, it&amp;#8217;s his first sleepover, I think he&amp;#8217;s ready and will be okay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 26, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-26-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 23:37:40 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-26-2019/</guid>
      <description>I got to sleep in, Bruce (Lesa) made me breakfast in bed. Kids got to play all day. Helped Ashley with her bracelet braider, helped Bruce with his puzzle, Dillan did fine with his car, and finally got to fly my drone. Dillan went to Gabe&amp;#8217;s for awhile, boys got their tablets, Ashley got my phone and her tablet, Dwyane danced and Bruce joined in. It was a pretty awesome day except for the kids fighting and bickering and complaining.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 15, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-15-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:19:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-15-2019/</guid>
      <description>Up until 4am doing the meditation, didn&amp;#8217;t fall asleep until an hour later, woke up when Lesa got up at 6a, then got woke up by kids at 7:30a. Gave the communion meditation, got a lot of positive feedback. Delivered communion to a home bound lady that made an impression on Ashley because Ashley prayed for her at lunch. Dillan went down to Gabe&amp;#8217;s, Lesa went to Walmart and Rural King, Ashley and Dwyane played in her room, Bruce played on Wii Console, and I actually got to nap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 8, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-8-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 22:19:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-8-2019/</guid>
      <description>Church, deacon in back. After lunch Lesa ran Christmas at the Zoo money to Amanda. I felt sick so tried to nap but butt hole neighbor was shooting. Dillan went down to Gabe&amp;#8217;s and Ashley went to Kaleena&amp;#8217;s. Boys played inside/outside. I put new straw and some Timothy hay in the rabbit hutch for Ashley. Kids got home at 5:00p and I turned on Indiana Jones, then they watched another right after.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 1, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-1-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 23:27:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-1-2019/</guid>
      <description>Planned on hunting, last day of season. Lesa wanted me to stay in to help with kids so I did. We went to church, Family Sunday, and basically chilled the afternoon away. Chilled as in Lesa and I didn&amp;#8217;t go anywhere or do much work. Lesa always works so that doesn&amp;#8217;t count. She did play a board game with the kids though, except Dillan who went to Gabe&amp;#8217;s. Kaleena was going to come down but not sure what happened there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 24, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-24-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 21:48:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-24-2019/</guid>
      <description>Was going to skip church and go deer hunting but Lesa would have had a rough time getting kids ready and there so I went with. Filled in as front deacon. I was messing around with Dillan during the sermon &amp;#8211; again, and Lesa got mad at us &amp;#8211; again. Dillan was missing homework again, got it online, and made him do it, he had a fit. Afterward he finished he went to Gabe&amp;#8217;s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 16, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-16-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 22:15:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-16-2019/</guid>
      <description>Up before everyone, opening day deer season, out before light, then in at 11a, and out again at 3p until dark. Didn&amp;#8217;t see a thing other than squirrels! Ashley had a Girl Scout ecology event in Hoosier National Forest on opening day of all day! That scares me to death! She climbed the fire tower. That scares me to death too! She came back to us by the grace of God.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 15, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-15-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 23:03:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-15-2019/</guid>
      <description>Church, lead deacon in back, security also. After church went to work and picked up Toyota 4-Runner I bought off Todd Davidson. Lesa followed me in Suburban and kids rode with me, they were excited to ride in something new and were amazed at the stick shift. Ashley went to Kaleena&amp;#8217;s and Dillan to Gabe&amp;#8217;s. Gary Flynn&amp;#8217;s son and grandson were riding their motorcycles around our loop, Dillan called them butt holes, whole thing exploded into an argument but sort of smoothed over but not really resolved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 14, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-14-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 23:32:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-14-2019/</guid>
      <description>Woke up about 4:00am in tent, took boys to bathroom, went back to sleep until 6:20am. Got up, another parent started stoking fire, I broke out camp stove and started coffee. Wound up making four pots for folks, and scrambling six dozen eggs. Dwyane ate nearly an entire bag of donuts, Bruce ate what he didn&amp;#8217;t. Broke camp after breakfast and took boys to Shoot-O-Ree. Their favorite things were fishing rod casting, Marshmallow shooters, and catapults.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 1, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-1-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 22:07:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-1-2019/</guid>
      <description>Woke up to Nerf gun fight in the house. Put a stop to that and started breakfast. Skipped church, everyone up too late, needed the sleep. Dillan and Gabe went to his house around 9, came back half-an-hour later with Gracie. All the kids had fun playing with each other even tough Lesa and I had our fill. They ate lunch with us and we sent them home. We discussed the night with Dillan and Ashley because we really didn&amp;#8217;t like some of the behavior we saw.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 31, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--august-31-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 01:34:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--august-31-2019/</guid>
      <description>Took Dillan to guitar lessons, not sure if he&amp;#8217;s learning anything but he seems to enjoy going, doesn&amp;#8217;t practice much. After lunch we all went with Lesa to get her hair cut at Fantastic Sams in Bedford and then went to Walmart to get Ashley some white tennis shoes for cheerleading. Let the kids get donuts too. Set up the tent for Dillan and Gabe, he&amp;#8217;s spending the night. Built a fire, we all joined in on marshmallows and s&amp;#8217;mores and hot dogs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 25, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-25-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 23:32:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-25-2019/</guid>
      <description>Slept in, skipped church, everyone needed the extra rest. Got a young opossum in the live trap; Dillan, Bruce and I released it near Springville Cemetery West. After lunch, we went to Mike Pearson&amp;#8217;s to discuss the house, going forward, Lesa is comfortable, more so than me. Kids took A/V ride down to Ken and Cassie&amp;#8217;s place, we picked them up there, they were getting A/V rides and checked out a cave on their property.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – August 18, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-18-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2019 23:02:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/08/status-update--august-18-2019/</guid>
      <description>Church, kid&amp;#8217;s first communion, Dillan spilled on his pants. Lesa took Ashley shopping for white sport bra for cheerleading. After chores Dillan went to Gabe&amp;#8217;s, boys tablet time. Ashley unloaded/loaded dishwasher, got tablet too. Kids total asses to each other. Wouldn&amp;#8217;t go to bed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>