<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kaleena Carpenter on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</title>
    <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/people/kaleena-carpenter/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kaleena Carpenter on The Williams Kids – Dillan ♥ Ashley ♥ Dwyane ♥ Bruce</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2013-{year} David E. Williams. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 23:03:28 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/people/kaleena-carpenter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – March 15, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-15-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 23:03:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/03/status-update--march-15-2020/</guid>
      <description>I woke up in a fever, took my temp, it was okay. Church canceled Sunday School, evening worship, Wednesday activities, everything but 10:30 worship service. They live-streamed the service. They also changed the way we do communion and offering. Pretty sparse attendance. We kept the kids with us. Right after church we went to Walmart and stocked up on more stuff. Couldn&amp;#8217;t find cereal or bread so hit three Dollar Generals on the way home from Walmart and still didn&amp;#8217;t find any.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 2, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-2-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:04:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-2-2020/</guid>
      <description>Lesa had kids fed when I got up, fixed me breakfast too. We went to church, Family Sunday but I was lead in back and also lobby security so didn&amp;#8217;t get to spend time with family. Had Dillan help again with communion and he did good. Ashley had all her Cincinnati Christian Girl Scout cookie orders and got most of them handed out and paid for. Kaleena called and asked Ashley to come down to play, Ashley ate lunch and got Springville cookie orders ready for Monday, and then went down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – February 1, 2020</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-1-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 03:19:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2020/02/status-update--february-1-2020/</guid>
      <description>Slept in sort of, still got woke up by Bruce running through the house. My phone was just an expensive paperweight this morning, wouldn&amp;#8217;t power on or anything. Finally able to get it reset and it came on, not sure what that was all about but thought I was going to have to get another and redo everything, kind of scary how we depend on them things. Skipped breakfast for lunch instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 8, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-8-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 22:19:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-8-2019/</guid>
      <description>Church, deacon in back. After lunch Lesa ran Christmas at the Zoo money to Amanda. I felt sick so tried to nap but butt hole neighbor was shooting. Dillan went down to Gabe&amp;#8217;s and Ashley went to Kaleena&amp;#8217;s. Boys played inside/outside. I put new straw and some Timothy hay in the rabbit hutch for Ashley. Kids got home at 5:00p and I turned on Indiana Jones, then they watched another right after.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – December 1, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-1-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 23:27:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/12/status-update--december-1-2019/</guid>
      <description>Planned on hunting, last day of season. Lesa wanted me to stay in to help with kids so I did. We went to church, Family Sunday, and basically chilled the afternoon away. Chilled as in Lesa and I didn&amp;#8217;t go anywhere or do much work. Lesa always works so that doesn&amp;#8217;t count. She did play a board game with the kids though, except Dillan who went to Gabe&amp;#8217;s. Kaleena was going to come down but not sure what happened there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – November 10, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-10-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 23:28:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/11/status-update--november-10-2019/</guid>
      <description>Church, Deacon in Back and Lobby Security. Afterward, we hooked up trailer and loaded bikes, got gas, and went to Paul and Andrea&amp;#8217;s for lunch with the Johnsons. Beautiful day for cookout. Kids rode bikes and had an awesome time and didn&amp;#8217;t want to leave. Got home and kids still rambunctious and played outside. Kaleena came over and ate with us. I got into a fight with Lesa and left for a couple of hours, had to decide whether I wanted to come back or not, came back for the kids&amp;#8217; sake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – October 20, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-20-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 00:06:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/10/status-update--october-20-2019/</guid>
      <description>Cincinnati Christian Church 100th Anniversary and they had a lunch and celebration, drew a huge crowd, all the deacons showed up at 9 and parked at library across the street. Ashley and Dillan came in early with me. Stayed for lunch and while kids played nine square outside we listened to some of the older folks stories about the church. It was kind of nice. Came home, kids played outside. Kaleena called, Ashley went to her house and the two of them showed up later at our house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 30, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-30-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 23:49:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-30-2019/</guid>
      <description>Barely made bus, kids ran to get on, Axsoms started yelling at Ashley. Tried asking what was up but they drove off, I followed, wound up in the parking lot of the liquor store in Oolitic. Axsoms said Ashley shoved Kensie getting on bus, and Kensie said Ashley made her eat paper and has been bullying her. I didn&amp;#8217;t see the shoving thing but the bullying did happen last week, and so I told them I&amp;#8217;d take care of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 15, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-15-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 23:03:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-15-2019/</guid>
      <description>Church, lead deacon in back, security also. After church went to work and picked up Toyota 4-Runner I bought off Todd Davidson. Lesa followed me in Suburban and kids rode with me, they were excited to ride in something new and were amazed at the stick shift. Ashley went to Kaleena&amp;#8217;s and Dillan to Gabe&amp;#8217;s. Gary Flynn&amp;#8217;s son and grandson were riding their motorcycles around our loop, Dillan called them butt holes, whole thing exploded into an argument but sort of smoothed over but not really resolved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Update – September 14, 2019</title>
      <link>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-14-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 23:32:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/davidewilliams/davidewilliams.github.io/2019/09/status-update--september-14-2019/</guid>
      <description>Woke up about 4:00am in tent, took boys to bathroom, went back to sleep until 6:20am. Got up, another parent started stoking fire, I broke out camp stove and started coffee. Wound up making four pots for folks, and scrambling six dozen eggs. Dwyane ate nearly an entire bag of donuts, Bruce ate what he didn&amp;#8217;t. Broke camp after breakfast and took boys to Shoot-O-Ree. Their favorite things were fishing rod casting, Marshmallow shooters, and catapults.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>